I will be in Tampa Florida I want to let
you know that from June 23rd to 25th
this Friday Saturday Sunday this weekend
that's right um seats are selling fast
I'm thankful for that and uh We've also
added more seats in Guilford New
Hampshire on July 20th at the Bank of
New Hampshire Pavilion U those are lawn
seats you can sit out on the lawn and
bring something I don't know what you
can bring you got to check with the
venue but maybe get you a little
um tapestry or something out that little
blanket and get out there and hug
somebody and giggle y'all can lay there
together in spoon and giggle if you want
and Hell take a damn pill or something
if you're doing pills I don't know I
don't do them we also have tickets
available in Edmonton Alberta on July
14th Grantville PA on July 19th Windsor
Ontario on August 18th Toronto Ontario
August 19th and Nia Gara Falls August
20th that's where you get all the
tickets
theo. thank you so much for supporting
the return of the Rat tour I want you to
check out the new Rat Life teas they're
in light blue salmon and sand and the
new Rat King big head teas hey Big Head
from Alaska to Nebraska baby you know
what I'm saying you want to tickle at
nickel I'm the fs with the bronze baby
all all that and more at theovon
store.com love you guys I want to thank
Rooster Teeth for allowing us uh time
today here in their Studio space out
here in Austin Texas we are grateful uh
to them and we are grateful for this
space today's guest is a comedian uh
he's a
podcaster um he's an I think I would say
he's an enlightened being um he has his
own podcast called the dunk trussle
Family
Hour um he has a show on Netflix he's
one of a kind today's guest is my friend
Mr Duncan
[Music]
trussle I'll sit and tell you my
stories
sh
me and I will find a song I will s
[Applause]
know they had a man by us that
uh they found a Korean guy who had been
hiding I guess in the ceiling of the
YMCA what yeah this was in um Santa
Monica they found a Korean in the
ceiling and so they uh they shut
everything down one time like the police
came in and raided him he'd been going
there for years you know he'd been like
sneaking he's like one of
those you know people are uh what's that
new thing people are hiding in people's
homes or whatever nesting yeah yeah
nesting yeah they nest in your house you
don't know they come down and drink your
milk right sorry yeah that's what's
going on it's like there was and this
guy was
nesting
um in the YMCA not a bad place to Nest
oh no and I would I remember I saw him
for years sorry Zach uh I was a bit
abrupt there I'm having a long I'm
having a long day and it's you are Theo
what happened well there's [__]
people in the ceiling brother there's
people in my ceiling right now you know
there's squatters I got Koreans in my
brain I got Brothers in my head who
knows what else yeah man it would be so
wonderful to have some brain scanning
device that showed you a visual
depiction of all the various entities
whatever they may be whether it's you
knowy olical structures are authentic
demons so you could just get the rundown
like when you get blood tests you know
yeah CU then You' know you you know like
why you're acting the way you act
sometimes not you specifically but you
know when the monster pops out oh well I
I think that that's you know I wonder a
lot if we do I was just talking about
this with on Rogan the other day if if
we do enough of the right testing like
like we take people's temperature like
that's such a temperature is such a who
cares you you can almost guess it you
know if you're just if you're anybody
with a thermometer with the two cents
you know finger yeah like you could be
you could touch somebody like oh you're
warm or you're cold you know you're dead
you're alive you know it's like but I
feel like it we just we have such
primitive testing it still feels like
that we're allowed to see right I would
love to know yeah what's what the f
who's in here today right what skeletons
are out yeah what unaddressed trauma is
about to explode out of me in the middle
of traffic yeah and then you'll know and
then maybe it won't happen but this is
yeah I man it's you know I think the
testing we have on the human body is
pretty remarkable right like you can do
like you don't even have to get the uh
what the prostate thing you know where
they shove the tube and cut the pops
it's disgusting it's like a haircut for
your intestines I got to get one soon
but the you could just do like a some
test that tells you if you know you've
got a problem yeah you don't have to get
the Michael Jackson drug and then have
this long tube that your doctor is
weirdly like excited to tell you about
yeah he's listening to Billy Jean while
he puts it in
you my doctor was so excited he's like
you'll be able to see your appendix like
I don't want to see my [__] appendix
I never want to see it I want to die
without seeing my appendix but anyway
now they can just test it I can't
remember what the name of it is the
worst commercial on TV it's like a like
a an annoying corrective animation like
interrupts people when they're swimming
and it's like have you had your [__]
checked yeah it's a stupid commercial
but the point is if they can do that
it's interesting the mind the mind is
like the ocean you know we have no idea
what's going on in there like it's the
biggest part of planet Earth and we
barely know what down there it's really
curious well the too man the ocean a lot
of it is most of the animals are by The
Edge yeah right like that you're talking
like down there in those thermal vents
it starts low population density and
what is down there is like Terri is
terrifying well it's the same type of
people that live I think if you get out
in a very rural Utah or you get out into
like you go deep into the mountains or
into some Caverns or something you find
some real cryptic homies out there oh my
dude you know when I was in Asheville uh
the last day of my kids preschool right
before we left I met a psychologist
whose job was to go out into deep
Appalachia and like you know it's that's
where all his clients were and just what
you're saying like the stuff going on
out there is crazy like he was telling
me one of his patients took a
scythe and went to this dude's trailer
where I guess he's sitting watching TV
and you used the Scythe to cut through
the trailer into the dude's back like
came through the wall the wall with a
scythe you're just watching like
American Ninja Challenge and a scythe
comes through your [__] trailer but
how interactive is that I mean you
couldn't no matter what cable you paid
for rarely would you be watching
American ninja and then an actual
bootleg [__] me ninja rolls up with a
scythe and cracks through your homestead
like 80% moonshine just just filled with
that kind of moonshine that makes your
eyes turn
white [__] something Sparks in his
brain he's like I'm gonna do it today he
goes and scye someone try it's a it's
it's crazy that's our minds they we have
our back roads and we have our dark
Bowers and secret places some people
never ever even know they just think
they're like the first thing that comes
to their mind they don't know that like
there's a lot of [__] down there yeah
they don't know that there's people
pushing people to the front of the class
to say something they think that oh
that's the first thought I have but they
don't know there's all these dark arts
and the distance pushing people forward
I think my mind a lot of time is like
what's that Black Street that they
burned down or whatever Zach that was
like a Hol that was like black it was
like
fancy it was like the first black like
Main
Street uh you talking about Black Wall
Street and Tulsa yeah that was yeah I
can pull that they burn it down they
burned it down a long time ago I'm not
sure what exactly happened
um it may have been racism it may have
just been fireworks I don't know what it
was white residents attack black
residents homes and business as well as
culture and public institutions in
Greenwood District of tuls Oklahoma and
oil boom City Black Wall Street one of
the wealthiest black communities it was
like kind of your early Atlanta Jesus
Christ they burn it all down yeah the
property loss 35 blocks were
systematically looted and
burned um yeah I don't know does it say
why they did
this I'm guessing it's not fireworks
yeah this looks more like probably
racism mobs of white
residents the Red Cross provided relief
uh do you see any if you if you see
something Zack let me know won't you
peep on it while we're um but that's
what kind of my head is you know I
remember going to the doctor one time
when I was young and the guy they put
that thing in your head that little
looker you
know the looker it like a they put oh
the ear looker yeah stethoscope it's
called an ear looker stethoscope y ear
looker yeah ear looker I got it well I
know yeah stethoscope they put it in
there and the guy was like oh you got a
bunch of uh Brothers in your head right
but he said the nword right the doctor
yeah and I remember that and I was
like and he was just joking around I
guess you know but I it was like I
didn't know what was going on how old
are you I was probably nine or 10 you
know just think of that dude like
imagine being that doctor looking in a
kid's ear and that is what makes sense
for you to say yeah and that's a doctor
he looked in he's like oh you got a
bunch of nword in your head and I was
like what
what the [__] well tell him to come out
dude at least like you know let's get on
a first name basis but it blew my mind I
think he was trying to like make my dad
laugh or something you know it was just
back in the days when there was just
kind of semi casual racism right you
know I I mean that's not even semi
casual racism that's like I mean if
we're going to like analyze racism
that's pretty hardcore like and that it
sounds like a joke he makes like that's
just his one of the funny bedside
manners things he does when he's with
nine-year-olds like that generally
cracks nine years olds up I guess it
would Terri would probably terrify me oh
I didn't know what was going on I didn't
know if like half of like In Living
Color was living in my there's humans in
my ear what are you talking you're a
doctor I'm GNA trust
you whoa yeah that's C so that was crazy
yeah it was just kind of the vi the the
environment around us I think at least
you remembered it man like that that's
the problem is like stuff happens like
that to you when you're a kid and you
forget it and then you get this like
weird little limp like a micro limp a
weird little like you have anxiety
attacks when you see ear Lookers or you
you don't know why that's the problem we
forget the Mind forgets but a lot of
stuff just gets in there just gets in
dude I
was like a few months ago I I don't know
man you know I've done psych Alex my
whole life so like if I get a little
wobbly generally I'm just like all right
whatever you're wobbly today but I was
like particularly like weird like I was
off I don't know how off you get but I
was like off off and my wife was like
what's going on with you and I'm you
know doing the Rolodex if I've been
eating a lot of Edibles am I getting
enough sleep you know and like
everything it's pretty normal and then
I'm like [__] I Google search cuz I try
not to remember it when my mom died MH
that day no didn't remember it didn't
remember the date but my body remembered
it and like talked to my friend who's a
psychiatrist he's like yeah that's
seasonal triggers they like activate
people's grief and some people don't
even know that's what's happening it's
so wild man that that's just stored in
us forever and what else is in there
yeah like surely it's not just the worst
thing that happened to you it's probably
lighter shades of things that and you
think that's your personality it just
triggers yeah a lot of our personality
is basically it's the foliage that's
built upon the sediment of the things
that have happened to us as as we grew
yeah man yeah you know it's really
fascinating I think um yeah I I wonder
how many two of those things can be like
triggers from previous generations even
you know yeah I mean I think there's a
lot of Investigation into that now
epigenetics yeah and also I mean you see
like a zygote or something or what's
that beautiful rock ever bought one of
those beautiful rocks and you crack it
open and it's got damn magic in it it's
just geodes yeah so cool God and you're
like wow this is in there you know yeah
right yeah right it's not all horrible
[__] inside of us I mean it's that's the
that's the thing like underneath all the
all whatever the weird neurotic foliage
you have is like for a lot of people
there's there's like things like that oh
yeah and these are a lot of women that
you know that didn't have kids or
whatever end up loving these things what
geod I didn't know that is that true
yeah these are like the Pringles for
women that couldn't
you know like uh didn't have a child I
think I did not know that man that's
cool yeah I didn't I guess I get it it's
kind of like a womb it's like this
universe in a womb or something well if
you really think about what would life
be like right if you thought about life
cuz I'm sure if you say you saw a little
bit of b a little bucket of uterus or a
bucket of not uterus but what's placenta
right if you saw a little placenta on
the ground you be like G look if you
didn't know it was placenta say you're
walking by you be like oh my God have
you seen live placenta a hippopotamus
sneezed over here no dude when I saw
plac for the first time when my wife
gave birth it's an alien like that is
not of this world it's the it's the
craziest thing you've ever seen and it's
just they just grow that man they can
just do that it's an organ that they
grow and then and then eject it's nuts
who does it who does what grows it well
I mean I'm assuming like it's something
you know the DNA it like you know once
you once you're pregnant it just sort of
it just their body's not oh women who
did you think I said I don't know I
thought someone was growing it somewhere
my friend's a placin farmer and he
invited me over and it was just you they
grow it in aquariums lots of jizz it's
basically chiz and honey and like you
know depending like everyone has a
different recipe yeah you have a bunch
of there's a bunch of Asians beating the
rice off of it out in like little boats
there's all kinds of ways to make plac
Theo these days especially my
grandmother's placenta recipe is insane
oh yeah dude yeah I've had paa I've had
placa it's like just depends on the
holiday you know oh my god when you get
a wonderful placa it's just so it's so
great harder to find these days I don't
mean to be like an old man and complain
but when I was younger you would get
like much better placentas oh the
Christmas placenta my grandparents would
bring over you God oh my God the smell
of fresh placa bubbling on the stove
cinnamon roasting on an open fire god it
was good and my grandmother would put
cinnamon on hers are you kidding
me it's so interesting man it's so
interesting yeah so this was like a big
in my family over Christmas dinner my
grandma my grand father was like why
don't we add cinnamon to the placenta
and like my grandmother just started
weeping walked out of the room so ever
since then I've been afraid to try it
but I've heard it gets you super high
yeah it's a real uh I mean it's brought
families together for years I think yeah
I think it's an American tradition I
don't know why people are against it
it's just like what you can you can
adapt you can adjust yeah having you
ever read Grapes of Wrath dude if we
that book was a half chapter away from
them eating a bowl of boiled placenta
that's right yeah just eat it eat the
binic eat whatever you want I mean the
last page of that book They're
breastfeeding off their own
sibling I think because they were so
starving in that book well I mean did
you hear like when they recovered Jim
Morrison's body in the bathtub in Paris
his mouth was full of placa a lot of
people think it was heroin that killed
him but like he got high and choked on
placenta oh like Parisian placent o
which is good oh yeah I'm not to sound
snobby but the I don't think anything
beats the placa of France yeah
plac you sound exactly like someone
serving placenta and Paris you've done
this you've been on the placa tours I
went on a whole placa bike tour of
Paris was best week of my life did you
guys see that uh Morgan Wallen is on
tour of course you did he's out there
who else is touring um the Harlem Globe
Trotters I believe are out there doing
it Willie Nelson maybe on his last tour
ever uh a lot of touring going on and
that's good timing for the newest
sponsor of the podcast which is
SeatGeek with over 28 million downloads
SeatGeek is the number one rated
ticketing app there are more than 70,000
events every single day on SeatGeek
including concerts Sports festivals and
more you know I went and saw Duran Duran
the other day or double Duran some
people call
them um and I got the tickets off seat
geek yes I did they've got tickets to
Tyler Childers Drake
Beyonce everyone they put all the
tickets across the web in one place to
make sure you're getting a good deal
each ticket is rated on a scale of 1 to
10 so look for the green dots green
means good red means bad every ticket is
backed by their buyer guarantee and
SeatGeek is the only site that lets you
return your ticket ahead of the event
with swaps that's how they do it and you
know I came through for you guys use my
code Theo for $20 off tickets at
SeatGeek that's right $20 off your first
purchase with promo code Theo make sure
you click the link in the description to
download the app thank you for
supporting live uh music and comedy and
anything you go see this episode is
brought to you by zip pics nicotine
toothpicks zip pcks Z
ppix brings you a totally satisfying
convenient and great tasting way to curb
your nicotine Cravings that's right if
you craving it Nick boy if you nicking
out you nicking around that's right
don't you think it's time you stop
putting smoke and vape oils in your
lungs I do now you can get your nicotine
fixed anytime anywhere without having to
rely on smoking or
Ving ziix toothpicks give you an easier
healthier and more discreet way to get
your fix baby get that hter they're
available in six rate flavors and they
have options in two milligrams and 3
milligrams of
nicotine that's right they're perfect
for flights sporting events restaurants
and literally everywhere else that's
smoking and vaping are banned zip pics
also offers caffeine and b12 infused
toothpicks if you're not a nicotine user
or if you're trying to get away from
your nicotine habit
it ditch the cigarettes ditch The Vape
and get some nicotine infused toothpicks
at ziix toothpicks
docomo at checkout your lungs will be
glad you did that's z p p
iix
toothpicks t o o t h p i c ks.com ziix
topi.com 10% off your first order by
using Code Theo at checkout must be 21
or older to order zip more smoke less
with ziix nicotine toothpicks that's
great dude yeah placenta man it is uh so
you saw it though when your wife had it
oh yeah you see it yeah you you see it I
mean well you save it like these like
these days they're actually recommending
that you like save the plac or I think
it's the plac like the idea is like in
the plac I could be wrong about this
maybe it's the umbilical cord there's
stem cells that the theoretically in the
next 10 20 years if you have access to
your stem cells from when you were first
born you could like reverse the aging
process so lots of people who can afford
it are saving their stem cells their
placenta I can't there's a name for it I
think it's called cord blood but all
that stuff like they cryogenically
freeze it and then down the line
theoretically you could like heal
yourself you could grow your body better
oh I would use that in heartbe I think I
would too what is that what are we
saving Zach you have any information on
that yeah cord blood is the right word
but it is people do like save and eat
the placenta um or bury it do you want I
have a picture of a placenta if you want
to see it i' would love to it's kind of
strong
though yeah okay yeah wow and is that
cooked or not cooked bring it back up
that looked like raw placa that's raw
yeah that's probably Chef Anthony
Bourdain's
kitchen or a cooking show or something
oh yeah this looks like a little bit
yeah this ain't no Wolf Gang Puck this
looks like this looks like real people
do eat this though you're right I've
heard that in La like women save the
placenta and literally put it in like
smoothies like that like people are
they'll like incorporate it into daily
eat it well there's a new purse too I
think they're doing a purse now you know
what the purse is beautiful Gucci has a
wonderful placenta purse for this season
a summer placenta purse but the um the
pro here's What's happen what happens
and uh it's a real problem is that
people bury their placa and they have a
little ceremony for it but they don't
bury it deep enough and their dogs dig
it up oh so like you go you're like
sitting down to watch TV and you look
and like there's like half eating
placenta on your
couch so you got to put it in a box or
bury it deep because dogs just love
placa who yeah I can't even it's
everything yeah it's everything a dog
would want it has blood in it it's like
from the crotch area you know it's like
dogs love all that oh my God it's yes
it's literally a dog's dream food yeah
for sure I
uh I I do think it is kind of
fascinating though that we don't have a
be like are we missing levels of
ourselves in basic scans and information
that like how close are we to be able to
do a scan an MRI that tells us
what's going on with ourselves at some
different levels like an emotional CAT
scan yeah emotional seems to be the
level that seems to be a lot of the
realm that we're really missing I feel
like when it comes
to uh
um uh like uh diagnosis yeah for yeah
for sure because all I mean all the
psychologist has to go on is what the
patient is telling them right that's it
you you can't you can't do anything
other than that or like past behaviors
or you know but still you don't know
yeah I mean this is to me the astounding
part of being human
is we're choosing to behave the way we
do like UL like you many times I would
like to think I didn't really have a
choice there like that that just was a
reaction to an event that spontaneously
erupted out of me
but if you kind of mindfully study your
worst moments most most of the time
you'll realize there was like a micro
moment where you decided to like do your
defense mechanism that always hurts
people's feelings or gives you uh a
feeling later of guilt or something
there's this weird micr second where you
decide to do it like your brain is some
kind of computer and it spits it's like
Choose Your Own Adventure and it spits
out a few options and you pick the most
annoying aggressive shitty one yes I do
you chose to do it it you know you
weren't possessed right but the choice
happen so quick that you could easily
miss the choice that's what's cool about
it is you don't have to be the way you
are at all change your clothes change
your haircut get a face tattoo whatever
you want you could do whatever you want
but we're addicted to being us you know
it's so habitual wow you know and it's
one thing I noticed with doing
meditation right that starts to help me
is I'm not
just like
in the carriage of the uh roller coaster
I'm on I'm not just because usually I'm
so attached to my own life I'm like oh
this is what but if I do some meditation
even for a couple weeks yeah I'm start
to have a little bit more separation
yeah from me and what I'm doing so I'm
like
oh I do have a little bit more choice I
can see a little bit more how I'm
behaving instead of just behaving like
if you're always up upset if you're
always anything or if you're feel like
you are just constantly in response to
some choices that that you're making and
you're like [__] I don't know what's
going on meditation has always given me
a little bit of a step backward it's
like oh I'm not always just the guy
sitting in the um in the roller coaster
car about to go on the ride now I'm
sometimes I'm the person waiting by the
side of it like I'm the conductor a
little yeah it's like oh interesting God
roller coaster is a great way to
describe it man there's a lot of
antiquated ways of describing it a
chariot attached to like the most
powerful horses and if you can't control
them you're going to get dragged wild
elephant wild elephant but you know
that's a you know this is an Eastern you
have to grow up in India to even know
like what that mean I mean I've seen
videos of wild elephants they're not
great but roller coaster that's [__]
awesome man roll roller coaster that's
the new DES destion of the Smooth
Operator good roller coaster it's a yeah
but just not being so attached to myself
I will say that that's the only time I'm
able to get any insight into like wow
look at my behaviors look at what's
going on instead of just being my
behaviors yeah yeah I mean and you know
something that's really wonderful is if
you it's not like you have that pause
that seems to expand with meditation so
you have a little more time to decide
what you're going to do you it doesn't
doesn't mean you're going to choose the
well- behaved thing to do it just means
if you do choose to be an [__] you
know you did on purpose you thought
about it and you're like I'm going to be
a [__] [__] here I'm deciding
instead of spontaneously just going
[__] mode right that's it that's what
meditation provides it provides you the
ability or the noticeability to go from
spontaneously being an [__] to
choosing to say hey I'm going to be an
[__] what a gift what a gift no you
know one thing I I don't know because I
haven't read this someone who was
friends with him told me that once he
ramdas the spiritual teacher say if an
if an [__] gets enlightened then
they're going to be an enlightened
[__] this whole notion that you start
meditating or take up the spiritual path
and like now like I don't know you're
making like Instagram video in front of
like Crystal Pools of water and in
beautiful forests with your beads and
your like emanating light that is not
the case it just you just like you're
saying you become the roller coaster
conductor at least you know that you are
simultaneously controlling the ride and
getting on the ride yes and there's some
freedom in that I think well it's
interesting because then you start to
see oh well what else could be going on
in the de depth of me when I'm not just
sitting here in the S like at the beach
of myself I'm not just you know it's
like I feel like that's one of the first
steps into sort of getting into
like realizing there's more to you than
just being this
reactive substance described as like a
human reactive substance is that what
the aliens call us that's probably what
they thought it was at first there just
like there's these re there's a bunch of
reactive substance on that planet yeah
we don't know what it is sometimes it
like gets into Vehicles we think it's
Vehicles yeah yeah on sometimes a doctor
tells one of one of them tells them they
have black guys in their head as a child
yeah I know well you know I did like I
did read that maybe that is the reason
even though these days I guess you can't
say we're not getting visited but one of
the theories on why aliens aren't coming
here is because they don't consider us
intelligent life yeah so they just see
us as some just like what you're saying
some kind of like vaguely sensient
reactive meat and not worth visiting I
think that makes sense I mean I've long
thought the reason why I think aliens
used to come a lot probably back in the
day right they came a lot that's why you
saw a lot of Egyptians drawing them yeah
you know and um and even the fact that
they would stay stable long enough for
an Egyptian to draw them because in you
know like they had to get a candle they
had to light it they had to get the guy
could draw like it was a little bit more
of than just chisel it yeah sometimes
chiseling yeah it was a more than just
us grabbing a phone right yeah but I
think yeah they used to come by a lot
and then they realized it's kind of
boring we've become like one of the
boring theme parks in the Galaxy so if
your parents if your alien parents take
you to the uh Earth for your graduation
I bet the other aliens like what a
[__] loser do your parents took you
to [__] nobody's been there in
Forever dude how how poor are you guys
it's like a Six Flags knockoff yes like
one of those shitty like shitty theme
parks where they don't even try to clean
up the puke yeah they're just pukes
splattered everywhere you'll probably
get like
pickpocketed you look at the kids
controlling the roller coaster and
they're like clearly on PCP they're not
paying attention you're people die you
know people die there but yeah the guy
yeah one of the guys running the rides
is in a coma but they have to hire like
the government you have more comos
people yeah they're just like yeah the
guy's like just like has his morphine
button and his [__] start the ride
button confused crazy I mean any theme
park I mean that is really like to me
the more terrifying than the roller
coaster itself is when you look at the
person controlling the roller coaster
and then imagine like what if that
person was controlling Subways in New
York ah would you feel okay about that
but the roller coaster is probably more
dangerous than the subway totally it's
like it shouldn't even work it's it's
like using weird physics they hired an
roller coaster architect they could
afford them for a couple of weeks threw
something together and then they just
let like a
17-year-old on like synthetic marijuana
for sure oh yeah control that [__]
thing yeah and then yeah yeah yeah and
then he spends he that kid he lobbies to
get a DJ there at the same time like for
the ride right like they're like we
could spend more money on safety and
he's like no way dude we need my boy
Ricky right here to spin his tables on
the side that's right and you know they
know they have insurance so they're just
like look I'm paying a [__] ton of money
for roller coaster insurance if someone
gets hurt they get [__] hurt we're
getting a DJ we're covered
legally this ISS the RM all the
night I think he's having a seizure I
think the roller Operator just had a
micro
seizure oh he's having a seizure dude
beat up the beat bro we got to [__]
drop the beat that'll help him dude I
was in the back of a [__] roller coaster
at a [__] theme park just like you're
describing yeah and whoever was that
like whoever's in charge of checking the
the straps comes back to me I was just a
kid man and she looks at me and she's
like you're not even supposed to be
sitting in the back the person next to
you to is he heavy there's a chance you
could break a rib
there wasn't I'm going to take you out
and put you in a different seat she just
said that as she's tightening the thing
that's holding me in the car and then it
just goes and she was right like the
person next to me was smashing it hurt
like it didn't break my rib it should
hurt man yeah it hurt it should hurt so
what kind of meditation do you do
Theo what I do is I wake up in the
morning I say a prayer I I do a reading
and then I do 10 minutes of meditation I
just close my eyes I just sit there and
if any thoughts come
up I try to uh just let them pass and
not attach to them cool I set my phone
timer for 10 minutes and that's it and
then I do like a written meditation
after that where I'll just write for 10
minutes straight just whatever comes
into my head stream of Consciousness
yeah that's great man you do that every
day mhm I've done that every day man I
would say or at least six days a week I
would say for probably the past few
months four months maybe wow that's
incredible good it makes me feel a
little bit more like like I'm okay to
think about stuff and not just be as
reactive sometimes yeah man I mean
that's amazing that's a long four months
of like that kind of practice is a big
deal yeah it feels pretty good man
um but yeah I think uh I went
to well let me think about that a little
bit more but yeah I think Earth I I do
believe then just going back to the
aliens thing that I think that Earth is
it's that old theme park where it's like
dude we're not driving all the way out
there there's nothing out there all the
information is these people are just
yeah trying to butt [__] and just
looking at you know and growing yard
drugs like we're not going over there
again I'm picturing the alien display
like the Star Trek display as that pops
up is what the analysis of planet Earth
is that's amazing there's like yeah
that's not worth our time yeah we're not
going to burn vespine crystals to
[__] go to that piece of [__] now it
will at some point though become hip
with alien youth to come back here and
do something because that's how
everything is right like at some point
it becomes cool to go to the uh to go
into graveyards like for you know
there's always like there's 20 years
where nobody gives a [__] about
graveyards nobody mentions them blah
blah blah blah blah even on Halloween
nobody's popping in but then something
flares up where great gra yards are
[__] popular again you know man I my
friend ran a graveyard and it was a big
problem Goths [__] on the graves
really yeah they had a problem with
Goths [__] on the graves and peacocks
wow the I guess the peacocks I can't
remember the problem with the peacocks
either they were like aggressive or they
were too loud or something but the main
problem was at night Goths would like
squirm in under the gate and just [__]
on graves for some reason it's like a
that's a bit like if you're running a
graveyard which by the way is apparently
like a very profitable business then you
have to have a plan for what to do when
people come and hump on the tombs
because there's some I don't know what
it is there's some kind of you know I
went jogging in that graveyard once and
I was so thirsty Theo and I uh I turn on
a spet and just drink some water and
then I realized I'm drinking [__]
graveyard this this is Graveyard water
this there's no way grave gravy
baby drink grave gravy yeah it didn't
taste good either man it had a weird
Tang to it yeah that [__] marrow son
god oh god dude you could sell that
though there's no way you couldn't sell
pure death filtered water grave water
grave water they already have what is it
like what's the new can water every
liquid death it's like that's their
premium yes bottled at a cemetery in new
orans that doesn't have great
sanitation so you are getting I don't
know if you've seen like have you ever
been to a [__] Cemetery speaking of [__]
theme parks you ever been to a non and
you smell you can smell the death and
some some of the graves like or the [__]
yeah they're hatched open a little bit
or somebody's yeah yeah people will get
in there people will steal a bone I
remember oh they love it well dude I
grew up in a neighborhood between a lot
of people would drive from like the main
thoroughfare in town and then they would
go through our neighborhood which was
pretty dumpy and go on to like kind of
wealthier
areas and we were right outside of the
city limits or the town limits I think
we lived in a town
but a lot of uh people would just throw
[__] out and once they got outside of
the city limits cuz there wasn't like a
um
you couldn't get a fine for it or
whatever so a lot of uh there was a
veterinarian that would throw out all
the animal [__] in our yard like into
our ditch by us right no yeah so they'd
have dead animal carcasses out there all
the time so we were always beating each
other with [__] you know [__] uh
be like ban fur and [__] just whipping
each other if you got a [__] big lab
German Shepherd [__] tibia that came
through boy we would beat the [__] out
of each other with that cuz you cuz for
sure they're telling the people who are
euthanizing their animals they're saying
to them don't worry we're going to
cremate these bodies and we're going to
give you the ashes yeah so what they
have is probably just a pile of Ash
because it's probably expensive to run a
cremation service for animals oh yeah so
you're they're sending fake Ash to the
like grieving dog owners barbecue ass
something probably out of a pit yeah and
so the dog owners have no idea that the
[__] vs are beating each other with
their beloved dog
spine Whoop That Trick remember that
song whoop that trip so sad but it was
crazy we'd have all the so we' we also
like we do like paleontology where like
make cool animals and bury them and like
there was some cool stuff like that but
yeah after a while my mom would get so
pissed because the yard would always
smell like dead animals you know Jesus
Christ so we had this abundance of like
dead animal smell which is a it's a
tough smell to enjoy your childhood in
to want to play in you know that's
horrible man it was bad and nobody cared
at the city man that's what made me hate
government right out the gate you know
is like if we had a little more money
they would have come and got the animals
out you know it's the beginning of a
horror movie for sure like somebody like
has their like demonic dog euthanized
and it's like you have to make sure you
cremate this [__] thing
like I'll create it sure there you go of
course we'll create it yeah I'll cremate
that [__] right now yeah don't worry
just throw it in the v's yard the boys
like to make art with the bones at one
little fella
yeah they start calling him que for no
reason like Jesus he's just playing with
the bones dude yeah that's how you know
for sure like that's really crazy man I
can't I I'm just trying to picture like
my childhood being
defined by the
waft of death that's dark man that's
dark how long did that go on for
probably I would say three years
probably maybe and the summer I think
was the worst because of the smell and
it would kind of happen in shifts it
wouldn't be like every day they would
throw stuff out there you know there
would be kind of a time of the month or
whatever I don't want to make it like
you
know you know whatever that's called
period or whatever but it would be like
a time of the month where the guy would
just come and toss it all out there
they'd run it through and toss it out at
night I wonder why he picked your house
well they just picked along our street
okay I got you so I think cuz it was
just right outside of City Limits you
know and I think they probably lived in
like some of the nicer area so they it
was kind of this pass through McGee
Street over there in Covington Louisiana
and people would just they throw all
kind of stuff out over there but you did
I remember this one girl had a little
collection of like the little neckl or
the dog little things like dog parts no
like little uh medallions you know some
dogs wear like uh oh the call she was
collecting their tags or something yeah
like some dogs wear little jewelry I
guess if they're like
[__] you know from Flor or whatever I
don't even know why they would do it but
they like bedazzled colors like like
like Trixie or something or fluffy or
but you know buddy or whatever yeah
that's weird man she had a little
collection of those but it was weird
[__] like that in our area you know they
had a prosthetic limb place by us and we
people were always we go in their
dumpster sometimes and get a [__]
extra limb out that [__] that's fun I
get that yeah but yeah I get that I
wouldn't and I I get like as a kid being
excited in some weird way about having
like animal carcasses in a ditch like
that is interesting there's something
cool about that was interesting but it's
going to get old that's all yeah and the
waft of it was bad that was the worst
part and I think my Mom hated that she
hated you know leaving us there and
being under the waft to those animals
probably you know cuz it it just haunts
everything well it's the smell of death
you're not supposed to like it like it's
supposed to tell you don't go here this
is a place that you might get killed
that's why we don't like it right this
is a place where you might get eaten
yeah it smells like death here that's a
bear ate somebody so don't go there yeah
so your your DNA is telling you you got
to get the [__] out of here man things
are dying here and and you just you're
forced to live
there yeah it was it was interesting SC
area man but yeah I think that's the
thing there will be a there will come a
time and maybe it's coming now because
aliens seems to be the you know gaining
popularity I don't know if it's gaining
popularity or if it's
gaining um like more sightings or
whatever what is this yeah this is
actually pretty topical NASA just held
like a 4-Hour press conference about
UFOs for the first time and they're
basically admitting that it's a daily
Occurrence at this point UFOs there
actually there's one thing that's
happened since this weirdly boring NASA
press conference where they did say this
did you see the thing there there's now
a
whistleblower who has come forward and
said that the United States has alien
spaceship wreckage and a congressman I
can't remember his name gave a statement
to the Press saying they were
debriefed that in fact we have alien
wreckage that that they're about to have
hearings on it so all the UFO people are
yeah that's the we're definitely not
alone thing people are really freaking
out right now because you know this is
what all the UFO people have been saying
is coming disclosure so yeah it's that
guy a whistleblower says he handed over
classified evidence proving that a
secret government program has been
recovering spaceships and aliens for
decades uh we're definitely not alone
David grush says uh he's a Former
Intelligence and Military
official um
H rep uh representative rep Republican
Dean Phillips a representative Dean
Phillips from Minnesota uh Democrat and
my first reaction is probably like
everybody watching this which is wow and
secondly I'll believe it when I see it I
mean that's fair you're not supposed to
immediately believe UFO oh no you but
but what's interesting about this is
that the denial that usually happens
when when things like someone says it's
not really happening in the same way and
again there was a
congressman who said we were debriefed
like did you ever see that cre so like
they did hearings on uaps a while ago
and then after the hearing they
debriefed the feds the Congress the
Congress they debriefed them and they
did an interview with one of these
representatives in the hallway after he
just got told whatever the [__] they
told himh and he's he said you can find
on YouTube he said something along the
lines of lock your doors and windows
tonight folks that was his response like
whatever they told him inspired him to
say we should like lock our doors like
this going keep an alien
out lock your doors after classified
hearing on UFOs a Louisiana senator now
we're talking yeah man this is the same
state that couldn't keep Brothers
outside of my head when I was a kid dude
I'm telling you you could like this is
nuts you can watch can are you allowed
to show YouTube videos on here there's a
clip of him doing it it's hilarious is
this him right here doing it oh yeah
that's it flying objects that a couple
of weeks ago our skies were
clear and then all of a sudden we have
spy balloons and other identified
unidentified flying objects raining down
on us like
confetti that is not
accurate um
these objects have been flying over us
for years many
years we've known about those objects
for many
years we're not sure that we've known
about all of them but we've known about
many of
them except for the Chinese spy balloon
we don't know what they
are what's different about the last two
weeks is that we've started shooting
them
down but we can't find the
remnants except for the the the uh the
the Spy balloon and that's what I took
away from the hearing today so I don't
know if he paid attention during the
whole hearing then no confetti raining
down like confetti it's a great
descriptor um yeah that's what I don't
yeah I
think but maybe I could see if there 's
an alien life form you shoot it you
whatever and it it dissip it's part of
the way it's constructed is not to fall
down to this that would be the first
thing I would make of something that
can't leave evidence right like exactly
but like based on the stuff that's
coming out right now and you know I love
UFOs in the same way I love like stories
about magic and miracles and I but I
don't go full bore into it because
ultimately like day-to-day reality isn't
impacted like you know mundane reality
like taking care of the kids paying the
mortgage you so you can get too
distracted by that stuff and spin out
but this moment in United States history
is really fascinating in the sense that
if we go back to Roswell it was a
weather balloon that's what they say
even though there's like many accounts
of people saying that they saw aliens
there was weird wreckage that uh seemed
to be able to like you could bend it out
of shape and it would go back into the
form it was just like weird [__] right
this gets uh denied by the government it
was wreckage weird stories about it
whatever we get Area 51 you know what I
mean like that has its own airplane that
flies people in you get a variety of
like early phase government
whistleblowers like Lazar I think is his
name the guy Alan Lazar Bob Lazar Bob
Lazar yeah Bazar uh you get like uh that
and then these people get creamed in the
media it's like that's a lunatic he
never worked to Area 51 this is [__]
he's like a con artist whatever but now
what's happening is instead of the
denial that generally follows the
whistleblowers admission of the US like
having some connection to aliens it's
not getting denied as much anymore and
in fact this whistleblower program they
just created makes it so anyone who
signed an NDA who's a private contractor
and has been assigned to work on alien
wreckage can now come forward and say I
worked on this [__] and they get full
immunity because that apparently was the
back door like you so there was a these
programs you could hire like I don't
know name any like Ron I don't know for
sure they I don't know if they have
records I'm just throwing out like
defense conton um hire durel dur H hire
duracel say look we've got this ship it
crashed can you guys hang on to it try
to reverse engineer it and so now a
private contractor has collected the
wreckage has the wreckage meaning if
you're asked under oath do we have
wreckage you could say no and because we
don't a private contractor has the
wreckage that was the loople so now they
set up this whistleblower program and
all these people like that guy are
starting to come out people who just
like worked at Hyundai or I don't know
worked at like Dodge Neon Dodge Neon and
they were like hey can you reverse
engineer this thing that seems to be
bending the time space continuum and
they're like no but they couldn't say
anything about it because they signed
these hardcore ndas so now they're all
leaking the data so we're getting this
weird slow leak from all these people
that's painting a picture and that's a
real program that they allow now how how
did that program get created The
Whistleblower program so what was
happening was um well the biggest
problem is like people apparently people
get around around these things and
everyone listening you can look all this
up it's like all it's I I've got the
documents it's real like it's not like
I'm just it's real you can find all this
stuff but the biggest problem is you're
a Navy pilot yeah and you see something
that is not functioning according to
your understanding not Kosher seems odd
it's going so fast it's stopping it's
just stopping like it's a a cursor on a
computer screen then it's going the
opposite Direction it's jamming your
radar it doesn't seem to have Windows
right so you see that and your choices
are do I say I saw what is obviously a
UFO and if you do you could really like
[__] your career up yeah so you couldn't
talk about it the other problem is that
apparently people who get too close to
these things they have there's a
physiological impact so let's imagine
you got close to one of these things and
now you're sick the VA won't pay for it
right because there are no us what are
you talking about and so inadvertently
you end up creating a situation where
people won't say what they're seeing up
in the sky right which isn't great if
you're trying to defend the sky we want
to know what's out there you want to
know everything that's flying through US
airspace right so yeah The Whistleblower
program was I think initially to kind of
create a safe way a safe haven where
people could say okay this is what I saw
I don't want to endanger myself I don't
want to endanger not being able to get
Medical Care and things like that that's
it yeah and and and then um and now it's
sort of like now that it's working
it's you know all you need is like one
person to come forward it's like me too
for aliens just one person then the next
person then the next person then the
next person you know that's what's
happening all these people who've kept
this [__] like completely secret I'm
sure bottled up imagine the people that
have molested people or something just
because they saw an alien and they
didn't how to process it or went insane
or like you know like like uh so many
things yeah beat their spouse or just
imagine a guy he he saw something in his
whole life he spent hiding things from
him like taking anything and hiding like
just weird there's weird ways that
people react to things that seem Beyond
them you know it eats you alive and then
add to it that apparently these people
have been threatened with death that
whoever's running this [__] is not
[__] around they they don't want the
general populace they don't want the
world to know that this has happened
because apparently and again this is
just conjecture here obviously from a
military perspective if you figure out
how those things can fly and you build a
fleet of them you it's like the new atom
bomb like you are have complete
superiority in the sky and like
if we're you're living in the United
States right now you want us to be the
ones you want them to be first you don't
want some other country who they
apparently all have this [__] to like
win this race but what about Mexico dog
you know they don't have the [__]
strongest they're like dog these
[__] dog that would be
incredible if all of a sudden they have
the most advanced Air
Force some guy just comes up with the
[__] and bro it's the lowest riding
UFO ever like UFO is only like 2 Ines
off the ground like dog this [__] is
[__] it goes it it goes too high dog
we don't this [__] goes too [__]
high that would be so sick dude it would
be you're right it would be interesting
like whoever gets it it's going to be
[__] cool we should have a show where
every country brings their brings their
latest like uh UFO aircraft that they
made bro amazing that would be the best
show skin care you know a lot of females
do it you see a female in God their skin
just looks like somebody just damn cared
about it like man is your SK what's your
SK who how much people care about your
skin well men often can't find the right
brand or simply lack knowledge and
understanding of skin care it's really
easy you want to wash your skin you want
to put a nice a nice base on it some
type of a conditioner uh moist
chizer and then you want to maybe throw
an SPF on there that's right that's
right if you're going to the mall and
you're going to go try and meet some
ladies you want to put something on
fellas you want to shine up a little bit
nothing crazy no Glitter nothing you
know nothing that's going to make the
you know somebody run out of a TGI
Fridays and hug here or whatever but you
want to look smooth and you want to look
comfortable and your skin wants to look
nice your skin is just B it's your skin
is the front door of your organs man
that's right Caldera lab is the leader
in men's skin care they have high
performance Goods they do and the
regimen bundle that they offer oo the
Clean Slate the base layer and the good
use our exclusive code Theo at Caldera
lab to enjoy 20% off their best products
that's Cal de
la.com to enjoy 20% off their best
products and I use Caldera I like it I
like Caldera I like putting it on and I
like feeling it on my face and feeling
joyous and happy get 20% off with our
code Theo at Caldera lab.com that's 20%
off at c lde r a lab.com by using Code
Theo take your health to the next level
in skincare with Caldera lab we've
reached that part of the show that
nobody ever skips and is sponsored by
Lucy nicotine that's right Lucy's tobacc
free gum pouches and Breakers are
intelligent nicotine options for
upstanding responsible adults like
yourself all Lucy products have three
things in common no tobacco
delicious
flavors and Powerful nicotine shipping
is always free and there's a 30-day
refund policy if you change your mind
you know I've been trying to ease off
vaping
and uh Lucy's Lucy sent me a bunch of
gum and I'm looking forward to trying
that out you know they got wonderful
flavors over there with their gum I know
they got
pomegranate
mint and mango they do them that's who
does it Lucy visit Lucy
ly. and use promo code Theo to get 20%
off your first order that's
lucy. promo code Cod Theo to receive 20%
off and always free shipping that's
right Lucy products are only for adults
of legal age and every order is age
verified warning this product contains
nicotine nicotine is an addictive
chemical dude I you know it's an
exciting time man it's like whatever it
is even if it's because at this point it
is exciting it's exciting like and what
are you going to do about it right what
are you going to do about it all you're
going to do is stay alive yeah hopefully
and yeah F you can't let it affect all
this stuff affect you that much like you
have to have some tongue and cheek look
at all of it right just enjoy the fact
that you get to live in a time period in
American history where the federal
government seems to no longer be denying
the thing that people have been saying
forever but here my question then would
be what's in it for the federal
government that they would now not deny
it well I think that's one of the most
important questions regarding this
situation is why why suddenly are they
kind of slow leaking this information
like I don't I don't know the answer to
that like I have no idea like well some
things could be I mean just off the top
of my head is if they want us to believe
in some sort of universal protector then
that will come along right like some
thing some organization some like
insurance against aliens in a way not an
actual like you pay 40 bucks a month but
like right like as in creating some new
world or you know if there's that part
of that regime that like you know this
this one world order type of thing if
they yeah you know I'm just trying to
think of The Upside what does somebody
gain um do we need a new enemy are they
realizing that like religion isn't
working enough on people anymore or the
fear of
there's not enough fear imposed on
people at the you know I don't know or
it could just be that that's blue beam
you're talking about blue beam that's
the big conspiracy theory that's like
essentially like there's two
possibilities the one you just said
which I guess if you're going to do like
aam's Razer that is the most likely one
right what is aam's Razer the mo the
simplest solution is generally the
solution so uh in this case it's more
likely this is a human operation than
aliens based on our understanding of
physics and the distance of
habitable galaxies where they have
planets in the Goldilocks region the
amount of time it would take to get here
based on what we understand about how
fast you can
go probably if if you're going to if
you're going to bet bet it's not an
alien right in Vegas if you're betting
you're probably you should always bet
that's not an alien that's a human thing
you're going to win most of the time so
uh that is one of the possibilities very
Sinister the idea being there's some
social control benefit related to
tricking the population of the planet
into thinking there's aliens that's
probably not the yakam razor of it then
I mean the other side of it is well we
live on a planet that's been being
visited by a variety of alien species
that more than likely genetically
engineered us a long time ago like sh
shifted us from Proto hominids into what
we are now probably for a reason that
we're not going to like like they like
were roombas or something I mean that's
one of the theories is they just wanted
gold so they genetically engineered us
to like gold so we Naturally Mine
[__] gold for them because we like
shiny [__] we like gold and that they
use it as some kind of fuel oh yeah have
you seen Basketball Wives dude no that
the whole show is about that oh gold
right they love gold it's crazy it's
what are we even doing here you right it
doesn't make sense like why do you like
this shiny stupid heavy [__] metal
why are you into that so much there's so
many other cooler Metals out there but
gold obsession is a real thing so the
theory is these anunaki programmed us to
like gold because they need it for their
spaceships they didn't give a [__] about
us they're just
like Farm some gold here brilliant from
that perspective so that that to me is
far more complex and and weird
explanation than just the
military-industrial complex has like
networked with other governments and
they're like I think they're at the
point they're so [__] dumb they're
going to believe there's aliens and like
we can manipulate them that's what it
seems like that's what it would seem
like to me because I don't
know unless it there there like we're
getting to the point where so many
people are being like there's so much
evidence the more you you make me think
this is not real the more I'm just
thinking you are not honest right like
at a certain point the the the residual
effect of the of the magic trick
isn't of it doesn't cause the beautiful
deception anymore it causes you to hate
the magician exactly exactly so that's
the thing that's weird bro is like you
know why why and look I would love to
see it would I like to meet an
alien I don't know
dude you would give me a break you know
just from our few podcasts together and
conversations we had I don't I wouldn't
you like it of course you'd like to meet
an alien it'd be the coolest thing ever
don't you want to know what they smell
like no one ever talks about that what
do they smell like what is the what is a
gray alien's head smell
like yeah is it bitter is it a stinky
smell is it
fishy oh if they're fishy dude I'm I'm
out that would suck bro how much would
the smell of aliens depend on how much
we give a [__] about them anymore a lot
huge bro if they smell anything like a
Korean pet store dude I'm [__] gone
dude Close Encounters of the Third Kind
spoiler if you haven't seen it I'm going
to spoil it very in the guy who's been
building the mud mountains happily walks
into the spaceship the Beautiful musical
spaceship imagine the [__] thing
closes and you catch that first waft of
deep like fish laying out in the beach
smell as you're like light speed heading
away from the planet that's going to be
what you smell forever as you look out
at the vastness of space black holes all
the beauty of space all you can think
about is there is just this stink
rotting eggs and [__] fish
bro we would hate them aliens
immediately we would hate him like these
stinky [__] smells so bad and
they refuse to like take showers and B
they're like no we don't do
that no we'll evaporate you before we'll
take a [__] shower no we are the
advanced intelligence you're supposed to
stink they're like no this is one of the
many things we figured out yeah if you
don't stink you haven't evolved like we
got we used to not stink and then we
learned we learned this is our purpose
here to emit foul odors dude I wonder
also the odors that we closet so much
now right like from shaving washing and
all the things that we do and use an
ointments how much of that we're like
taking out of like how much other stuff
would I gather about you if you came in
with two say 80 Days of hot smell on you
80 Days of fresh Duncan on you post
Burning Man Duncan yeah you come [__]
rolling in you've been hugging your kids
you've been with your wife you worked a
couple of long weeks right you [__]
been on seven flights like but you get
the full like I wonder how much are we
killing off like some of that to go back
to that like scan of people like how
much of that was in our brains that we
knew how to scan that we were be able
that we were create able to gather more
right like what if we were the aliens
initially I got you and we've dumbed our
or we've we've killed off all of those
things I gotcha yeah man I gotta it's
like uh the the there was this I heard
of this study where they took and I
don't know how they did this and um I'm
not a scientist and honestly when I hear
about studies maybe one out of a 100 I
try to actually read the study and then
when I do try I realize how dumb I am
I'm like I don't understand statistics
but so all that being said apparently
they a study they found like good
genetic matches for uh women and they
like based on their genetics and this
person's genetics somehow this is like
they would theoretically make a great
baby so they take these dude's
shirts put them in Ziploc bags and they
let the
women uh just smell the shirts so the
women are like smelling like you know 10
shirts and they're like pick the one
that you would want to go on a date with
right and so apparently all of them
picked the right genetic match based on
the stink of the shirt wow but the ones
who didn't they were on birth control so
there was some weird connection to like
something about that was cutting off
what you're talking about the ability to
discern from someone's stink it's some
subliminal level what's going on with it
and yeah man it's a good question like
how much of the problems we're having
right now are just because we don't
stink enough like we're supposed to
smell you're supposed to smell horrible
all day long honest stink good stink I
would hate that world though man I would
I I like not stinking yeah I've grown
accustomed to it now if you Gateway
stank me if you did some Gateway
stanking where like you somebody stopped
by this stank or you put me in an Uber
for four minutes and like oh that guy
and then you next day you do me a six
minute Uber and then two days later I
have to you know I have to stay sleep
overnight at a buddy's apartment who's
lives right next door to like uh you
know uh can canabury row or whatever
what was that guy place that that guy
always talked about caner row Canary row
right so like if you keep upping the
sank on me where
eventually I [__] wanted something
that stank yeah you know what I'm saying
I wanted to meet a [__] by the sand in
in [__] in uh aaho it's hot you know
or in kohi or somewhere it's nice isn't
it it's nice the the nonsterilized human
it's not like it's a terrible smell and
you know how much of what we consider to
be like Bo is actually just all the
weird [__] they put in our food how much
of it is just our body's desperate
attempts to
vent like Cheetos where your body's like
I got to get this [__] out it's like you
know they're dumping Fukushima right now
they don't know what to do with the fuk
radioactive water and they're dumping it
in the ocean it's like that our bodies
are just trying to get the poisons out
of us like you know like think of like
when you drink a lot that next day you
smell like booze it's so gross oh it's
crazy we've had on the uh when we're
touring we've had tour manager uh tour
uh people come on the tour who drink a
lot and in the morning you'll walk
through like the little B like the part
where the bunks are and the people are
sleeping in there yeah and it be like oh
my God and you can since I don't drink I
can smell almost what they've had
sometimes it's crazy like they've had
beer they've had Voda uh and and and or
when you're pissed smells like coffee I
don't know if that's you know that's or
I don't know if You' ever eaten so much
weed that your boo starts smelling like
weed it happens it's just you know it
happens and I've heard now this is
probably [__] that probably isn't
like Saints like gurus people who've
meditated their whole lives who've
gained Enlightenment they smell
different like they they smell sweet and
perfumey like the original smell of
humans was or I look at Filipinos what
do you mean they I mean Filipinos I
could have named seven Filipinos that
don't smell good really or wait you're
using them as an example of of like a
bad smell no I think they're enlightened
people oh they smell good oh I gotta man
I mean it's probably a mark against me
that I'm not familiar with the smell of
Filipino
that's sad I wonder if one ethnicity
doesn't filter as well as the other I'm
sure we all have so many differences um
Whitney cumins is having a baby what
that's amazing I didn't know that that's
so cool wow when did when did that she I
smelled it on her you smelled the
baby
been what's that huh you're growing life
Whitney m see I bet in the old days that
was possible there's no way you couldn't
roll up on somebody and smell if they
were in a
relationship if they had if they were
sad yeah if they
were if they had probably defecated
recently if they had had a birthday
right you just named everything that
happened to me
today the the the um but there's a think
about all the things in his smell that
because it's like we don't there's a lot
of stuff dude sight gives you so many
Clues bro you ever been on a little bit
of mushrooms or something or done some
IAS and you can tell somebody's entire
life story by looking right in their
eyes and you're right dude this is why I
don't do acid in public anymore because
like you might be having a great time
but then all of a sudden for whatever
reason you literally
experience a person's Consciousness like
it transfers to you yeah you see the
pain you see the sadness the anger the
bitterness the Heartbreak and you just
wanted to have fun you wanted to go out
to a bar and drink but suddenly you're
being inundated by a person you're like
what happened to you yeah man that's and
they're like Randy's dead and you're
like God is that I think this is why
like clar voyant you hear clar voyant
complain and stuff or like psychics or
whatever they don't like it they don't
want to be sensitive like that because
that's their daily experience is just
getting blasted by people's Karma and it
hurts and you don't know what to do yeah
I could imagine that I think there's
also probably a lot of lazy psychics out
there yeah for sure and they're like H
yeah here comes a little bit more
information about you know Brenda you
know they don't give it all they know
it'll open a can of worms I'm going to
[__] ignore that their grandmother is
like talking to the psychic she killed
me she [__] burned my body in
hydrochloric acid poured me in Theo
Von's
yard please call the police and the p is
like I [__] that the is like Grandma
says hello yeah she loves you she loves
you she loves you she's happy you're
doing well yeah and she just wanted me
to say yes she just she thinks you have
a beautiful yard or something she like
makes it yeah that sucks man that I
don't like I don't like getting around
psychics because and also Mass's I get
creeped out by because I feel like
sometimes they you know massas are often
weirdly psychic cuz they're touching
bodies all day and I get creeped out
like are you detecting something right
are you sensing
some psychic blockage that I need to be
working on that you're afraid to tell me
makes sense that they can do it some of
them can you know they have all those
raiki healers and those people that are
really what is raiki let's bring it up
Zachary
please have you heard of this stuff
yeah it's therapy raiki therapy is a way
of guiding energy
throughout
uh guiding energy is based on the idea
that we all have an unseen life force
energy that flows through our bodies
according to the international center
for raike training a raiki practitioner
gently moves her hands so it seems to be
and I've seen this as well I've only
been offered raiki from a woman removes
her hands just above or on the client's
clothed body with the intention of
reducing stress and promoting healing by
encouraging a healthy flow of
energy yeah it's like how much of a
vessel are we let me hit that
River you got it man I was feeling
guilty oh no don't do it huh don't
re-trigger it
man don't re-trigger it Theo it's a
horrible addiction I know it is I want
out I've been thinking about getting
acupuncture like it go ahead it's
actually very good Vape it's a nice
flavor what do you think isn't that
great it is really good man I'm
sorry it's okay this is our sorry no I
came in here and poisoned you it's a
contagion I triggered your react I
triggered you you had to have it I'm so
sorry this the problem I you when you're
an it's good and also that particular
one has this weird heft to it that I
like yeah it feels sturdier kind of like
a uh Jeep Grand cheran
yeah like a Carpenters Vape it's like a
industrial Vape keep on the
Belt you know energy blockage man that
does it to me yes this is like this is
what I don't want to get into Vape
lecturing anyone everyone's addicted to
this [__] right now but the I like I'm
listening to this great book I think
it's called why we
meditate it's so good uh and basically
the idea
is many people
me included are in a hurry rushing
around and the reason we're in a hurry
is because we have this Speedy kind of
energy in our chest it's that feeling
when you're like [__] I got to go I got
to do this that thing you should have
seen me when I rolled in here I'm sorry
Zach I want to apologize again me too I
was I know I you know I was excited to
do to see you but also I'm like [__] I'm
late you're doing this weird Speedy
thing well the the what's triggering
that is energy that you know anyone who
out there is anxious or feeling in a
hurry or freaked out right now you could
just tune into it like easily you just
feel it it's like a fast kind of uh
buzzing sort of weird energy in your
chest generally or um it's hard to get
rid of it well that right right well
it's a block it's so according to this
book that energy is supposed to be under
your belly butt not up in your chest
like your that your Energy's gotten all
[__] up but now it's all stuck in your
chest and so like via like meditation
breathing
exercises you the idea is over time you
sort of retrain yourself to get that
energy throughout your whole body it's
like it's not supposed to be just here
the imagine if you could spread it out
like nice peanut butter over your entire
psychic body that would be very powerful
it's just not supposed to be right
you're not supposed to be freebasing the
[Laughter]
anxiety yeah I feel like that's the
culture we're in now now where we are
freebasing our own anxiety yeah man we
have boiled it down to like just a
granular powerful Rock it's like fentel
we've done the same thing fentel did for
heroin we just figured out a way to just
hyper accentuate our anxiety and coffee
doesn't help I mean a in Red Bull
nothing helps man sorry to yawn in here
but I think that was like my body's
saying hey man we're trying to slow it
down do you feel overwhelmed I'm sorry
to cut you off
you have one of the top podcasts right
now uh we've been fortunate and I want
to come on your show too thank you I owe
you that thank you I know a few years
ago we had talked about it and I think I
don't know if you asked me or not and
then I think the pmic happened and I
think I said that I was I there was a
time where I was going through a space
where I could barely even talk to people
at all oh my God so um but let's get
that done here and if I don't know if
you can do it over Zoom if not I'll Zoom
it's all I mine's easy it's all remote
you don't have to be anywhere at your
convenience you're busy man you're
touring all the time but I want to do it
soon I want to do it in the next month
or two so that we can uh I want to bury
that that's been a little bit of a
hatchet for me in my life I know I
brought it up I well I said I wanted to
do it and never did it thank you Theo
apology accepted it's it's so fun just
to spend time with you same that's what
I'm realizing I'm like I'm realizing I'm
missing out sometimes on uh getting to
spend time with people because I get so
caught up in my own responsibilities
well podcasts or friendship dates did
you you know that that's what it is it's
a date for friendship it's how I just
realized that the other day I real I
went I went to do Rogan and I knew I was
going to be in town for a bit but he's
so busy I mean he's like I can't even
imagine how how just busy are
responsibilities he has he's also a
father you're a father like so I
realized man I should have used that
time with him on the show to be our
friendship time and sometimes I think of
those times more as
like I do think of but as but I could
have brought to him more like questions
I have about things where like I could
have used some guidance or some
suggestions or yeah um sometimes I I I
don't know why I sometimes don't do that
you know and I think with Joe we're
still getting to know each other some
yeah and his is such a big show I think
you are nervous as well but um you know
that is like the abyss of that show is
the moment you start thinking about how
many people watch it it's scary if you
let your mind go there man that is a I
really try not to do that like before I
do his show it's so easy to like think
about that and then you're like Jesus
[__] Christ this is like the top
podcast on Earth but yours is like the
second I saw it we were scrolling
through something I don't know what it
was but I mean [__] we've been real
fortunate man you know we've been real
fortunate well you're funny too I mean
it's also you're super funny I see your
stuff pop up on my my wife makes fun of
me cuz I do Instagram reals instead of
Tik Tok and she thinks that's an old man
thing to do oh really but your stuff
pops up a lot it's very it's like I love
watching it like it always makes me
laugh yeah we got all kinds of neat
stuff out there well I think also you're
such a unique thinker man I think that
um that we need we're going to need you
more and more in the future are you
feeling that that whatever gifts you
were kind of given like cuz I know in
the beginning you were basically really
just a comedian right yeah was that your
original goal dude I wish I could say I
had an original goal that's my problem
it's so malleable malleable chaotic and
also I I really try as much as possible
not out of some not spiritual High Road
in here but I man I try to stay in the
present moment not because of this is
where you should be to find peace but
because man when I go too far up here or
I go into the future or I go into the
past I just freak the [__] out yeah but
if I'm like here in the moment and just
letting like the moment happen it's so
wonderful and so and then when I start
thinking like what the [__] am I am I a
podcaster a comedian and am I a voice
actor what the [__] am I I freak out
because it's like I have no idea yeah so
it just seems easier to be like all
right let's just go with the punches and
be who I am yeah right and hope for the
[__] best right because that's all
you can can really do I mean honestly
like looking at the world right now as
it is it's like come on like are we
really going to have a next week right
you think we're going to have a next
month I don't know I mean there's aliens
on the front porch there's [__]
people are fighting we don't even know
who's really behind the fighting there's
like old war debts and like IUS from
companies that are like from Black Rock
and Slumber J that probably still are
Milling around in the disc
people haveed Wars that we don't even if
they were given the right reason they
were fighting for Oh you mean the the
the the this is the crazy thing about
the Russia thing man these these are
conscripts like everyone conscript it
means that you are drafted and and uh
the the real problem with all the people
celebrating the death of of Russian
soldiers like like their [__] blowup
dolls is that you I get not liking a a
dictator Putin and [__] invaded
Ukraine [__] you but you can't forget
and this is the Paradox a lot of those
people on the front lines getting blown
up by drones were political prisoners
right that got forced to go fight in a
goddamn meat grinder by the dude who
arrested them because they tried to get
him out of office wow imagine that you
know what I mean man it's really sad
it's like these are I mean I don't know
who's in jail in Russia I imagine
there's some really scary people in
Russian jails who did horrible things
but I know for sure a lot of people in
Russian jails are people who just
protested like the government yeah and
those are the ones who are on the front
[__] lines so it's like you can't
really celebrate the fact that some
majority or some some percentage of them
are like were actually activists some
percentage of them were just trying to
make more democ happened in Russia and
they got arrested so yeah man exactly
World War III all the by the way I'm I
don't I'm not trying to get all negative
here no we're just looking at the
landscape of things I think most people
are thinking that but but here right now
hanging out with you talking telling
stories and and for most people you know
this moment is so beautiful yeah look
how beautiful even like in a podcast
Studio where there's like cameras and
lights just like how cool it is just to
exist there's color and oh yeah existing
is great man you have and you have to
remember that that hey at least I get to
be here for whatever this is yeah at
least nature gave me like I've gotten to
come to the edge of the Fishbowl for a
moment and whatever the existence of the
universe is and have open eyes and see
something like yeah you know what I'm
saying like it's all going to [__]
disappear so it's like the fact that
we're even getting to see a little bit
of it or have feelings like love or um
jerking off or hugging somebody or
eating some salmon or something you're
having some you know you get to have
some unique moments or having a child
and hugging your child getting your
child a um you know a chocolate or
something you know it's nice man it's
the best and and that like the thing
I've realized lately is the amount of
anxiety or worry that I'm experiencing
the present moment if I let myself worry
about some future catastroph
is actually worse than if the
catastrophe happened you have you know
what I'm talking about like totally like
you imagine the thing you're most afraid
of happening whatever it may be and then
think about how bad you feel as you
worry over it versus the day after that
rotten thing happens so it's like you're
worse off and it hasn't even happened
than if it did happen yeah you're
already suffering yes an outcome that
you don't even know if it's real or not
and nine out of 10 times it's not as bad
not as bad nine out of 10 times whatever
it is I mean obviously there's a few
things that are going to be worse than
feeling anxious getting like slowly
eaten by a bear yeah that's going to be
worse than like whatever your emotional
state is but most things pretty C and I
probably death too I imagine I imagine
death is like the ultimate version of
like [__] I spent my whole life worrying
about this right this is real chill this
is great yeah it's probably going
through one of those turns style things
like it's a little wonky at first and
you bump into it and you're like oh this
thing doesn't even [__] open do I
have the right thing and then it opens
you're like oh oh right here we are here
we are again this is where I always come
and it's beautiful and my every single
day I was like trying to protect myself
from this oh you know what I'll do it
again and then you reincarnate again and
eventually maybe you figure it out do
you think everybody gets drafted for
reincarnation I don't think so what do
you mean
um do you think God redrafts does
everybody get drafted for reincarnation
you like apparent like the model I like
for
reincarnation is that it is
uh that you don't have to but you
probably will and that you've been doing
it forever like the amount of time if
you're a human you've been
incarnating so many times it's
impossible to even imagine how long
you've been reappearing I don't know
some people are brand new humans though
you ever get that fresh out the box
[__] you're like Dam this is
your this is your first lap on this Pony
homie you
know he's like trying to get on the
horse he's like I don't know what to do
you know I've been a bumblebee for the
last 6,000 incarnations you want me to
suddenly be a [__] human drive a
car yeah man yeah I I I think it's
possible he's just [__] driving Uber
and just just hand eating hand eating
honey out of a jar the whole time I was
a fly I was a slug and I'm a human now
that's it that's patience have patience
those people should have a little sign
on that says look this is the last seven
things I was so cut me a little bit of
slack here like damn this guy was a
daddy long legs four times in a row I
was a bacteria and now he's Luca donic
Jesus Christ man
have some have some have some support
for the guy give him a
break yeah you're right it's like it's
[__] it's like there's all these old
souls floating around like acting like
this human thing is easy flowing with
every
moment making it see it's like no [__]
you you're like the guy at the gym
you're like the guy at the gym with a
six-pack and the perfect [__] body
who's been working out their whole lives
and that belt and he has the weight just
hanging off the belt the whole time he's
at the gym what is that what is that
that's crazy it's crazy yeah I mean I
think this is why I love even if it's
not real reincarnation as a method for
self for being compassionate to yourself
because it's like you don't know what
you were in your last lifetime you want
to talk about epigenetics affecting
current behavior patterns according to
these ideas your past lives and
decisions you've made in your past lives
are flowering right now and at the
present moment so when you're beating
yourself up you know about this or that
it could be that really what you're
experiencing is karma from the time you
thought it would be funny to grab the
baby out of the baby carriage and throw
it in front of a truck or something in
the early 40s you know what I mean you
don't know what the the the the bad luck
you're experiencing is necessarily
originating from right this could be
yeah this could be some guy a previous
lifesuit you're you're paying the debts
of a previous existence ex exactly so
just take it easy on yourself take it
easy on yourself because it's who knows
well it's hard to stom and I think
though that if we lived still in tribal
communities and stuff and there was a
lot more connectivity between past lives
and we honored like who had died
previously and this and that and we were
still connected to them I think then you
would have more like compassion from
your group like oh what you're dealing
with now is what grandfather soand so
did and you know it's still making its
way out of the uh yes out of the DNA
back into nature
um yeah Whitney's having that baby man
congratulations mlov Whitney that's
great that's great it's so cool it's the
best thing I never did you guys ever
date you and Whitney no yeah I mean NE
never
did did you want
it probably I I I think maybe you know I
wouldn't have minded maybe a date or
something probably yeah of
course I think there's something that
happens as you get older if you don't
have a family when women start to get
knocked up or when people start to
sparse off my best friend Scott just got
engaged where you start thinking like oh
oh [__] I know what you're talking about
you're experiencing a version of what
we're all going to experience in our 70s
my meditation teachers teacher Chim CH
said to him when you get old your
friends start dying like flies just
dying so now what you're experiencing is
like pre- death they're going into a new
life they're being reincarnated as a
parent and you know no matter what
they're saying no matter how much
comfort they may or may not be offering
you regarding their presence in your
life you know it's just not they're
they're going to Blink out of your
reality for a little bit it's going to
change yeah it's going to change it has
to there everything shifts everything
and you there's just like no way around
that I mean kids are a it's a full-time
experience you you want to hang out yeah
and and you know what we experience the
the Breeders we
experience our friends eventually being
like not asking us if we want to go get
a drink anymore cuz they know cuz every
time they ask like [__] got to get a
babysit oh I can't I'm doing this or
that and then so it s it sucks at that
level man I mean it takes extra
discipline wow I'm sorry man you know
what you maybe it's time yeah to start
seeking your uh life partner I think
some of that is true too you know I
think I had well when I went to and I
did IAS I think it was probably maybe a
year ago right and so that was the first
time that I started having an experience
with like the younger me like the child
me you know and realizing that I just
had never wanted to grow up because I
never got to be the child I wanted to be
right I had this and I'm not like having
self-pity I'm not trying to just like oh
but there was a lot of I think I had
held a huge grudge
against the world and then of just life
the way things had played out that I
hadn't gotten to have the childhood I
wanted you know right or and there
wasn't enough lessons in it that helped
me to easily adapt into the world and so
I uh but I didn't realize that until
Iowaska cuz then you're right there with
your younger self you know yeah and that
was pretty crazy be like oh
wow um you know it's time for me
[Music]
to be an apparent somebody at some point
has to be a parent to this child inside
of me otherwise I'll just forever be
this child inside of me so if I want to
have a an adult life as well then I'm
going to have to start to evolve some
you know yeah and some of that's kind of
sad because you're let you're basically
watching this child like you know you're
helping this child grow up but you're
letting this child know like
hey you know I I'll take it from here I
love you I'm going to take care of you
um you're not going to be able to run
the show all the time anymore cuz we got
to grow up you know yeah yeah and you
know it's being a parent you go through
these little micro griefs because you
know it starts off you are so in love
with this baby you're so in love with
like how like just what it feels like to
hold your kid but they obviously they
grow yeah and that baby goes away it's
gone and you're there's there's a perod
like [__] this is so sad this like
beautiful like kid is going to like like
change into something else but then the
next phase you realize oh I love what
this being is becoming and and so that
but that moment that weird Lial moment
between like like lives because you know
I think people reincarnate in a lifetime
like what you're talking about it is a
weird form of it's not obviously it's
not physical death yeah but it is you're
letting go of some of something oh it
feels like that a lot yeah man it really
does I can feel it I can there's moments
I have where I can feel it and I can
feel myself doing certain things that
are like okay I'm going to put this
child to B you know put this young not
let this you know this child's going to
start to grow up you know he has to it's
been too long if he wants to have a
family of his own if he wants to be a
father and be these things he's going to
have to dude you'd be a great dad you
know the gift of having a sort of
tumultuous childhood is that you uh you
when you have a kid like I mean you get
to fix that a little bit like you you
won't fix it completely like it's so
crazy when like aspects of your parents
that maybe weren't the most evolved
bubble out of you oh yeah and you
realize [__] this is why my parents were
acting the way they were acting they
tried to stop this thing too it's very
hard it but you you have a real reason
to evolve because you don't want to like
impact your kids in in a dark way so man
I'm telling you from a like
spiritual like the it's a it's a brain
scan man like you will understand so
much more about your parents who mainly
how much they loved
you mainly you'll understand holy [__]
they love me so much there's no way you
can't feel this for your kid and they
tried their best they tried their
[__] best and they and and and that's
a really wild thing cuz then you have to
forgive them like if you were carrying a
chip on your shoulder about this or that
it'll the chip will dissolve a little
bit but oh I got a [__] 12pack of
Pringles on my back D I've carried them
I've carried them I think that's a lot
of Pringles man I yeah I've carried him
a lot I've tried to get I've tried you
know I do 12 step I'm trying to get
through some of it I just have to work a
little bit hard harder and some of it
takes time too you know I've always been
a slow evolver I've been a really hard
decider in my life everything is really
slow so yeah man some of it's just who I
am you know slow is good fast is
suspicious slow means you like when you
do slow change that's real change fast
change whenever I do Fast Change makes
me nervous that's like monthong you know
it'll last for a month when I do a fast
you know whatever the [__] thing is
and you should be suspicious of anyone
pitching Fast Change to you yeah it
doesn't really work like that it's slow
and it's supposed to be and you don't
need to be anything other than the way
you are right now man like that's just
fine like this is fine like the I'll
tell you when I met my wife like I'd
heard all these cheesy [__] who got
married and a kids say I knew she was we
were going to get married I knew we were
going to have kids and I was like okay
whatever that's such hor [__] yeah and
then it happened to me it it wasn't like
like I what happened you just started
talking to her and what happened let me
hit that Ripper one more time you got it
man what happened was the best it's
like you know this it's like you watch
people who put their foot in fast moving
water and it's just like they're gone
it's like that you know like the the the
the the concept of control when it comes
to like dating and finding someone that
you decide to like spend your life with
I think it's a little naive like I think
there's big big gears in the universe
that we can't see like behind the watch
face that are just turning and I know
this sounds so new Agy and cheesy but
sometimes I think it's like you meet the
person at just the right time because
the souls of your kids are ready to come
into the universe at that
that makes sense like you know what I
mean like right now your kids could be
like in their 70s or 60s right now in a
previous life about to expire in a few
years and then they're ready to pop back
in yeah and that's when you meet the the
person who they've they choose you and
then they bring you together and then
you you are like that's when it happens
yeah I just I mean again obviously this
is probably just horeshit but I when
you're like when it happens you realize
like I don't know how much of this I had
control over I don't know how much I
chose this and how much I was chosen for
it and so that means go slow
yeah yeah no that's a really that's
really nice to think on that's really
nice to just kind of yeah because it
takes some of the pressure off of you
like I don't feel a pressure to meet
somebody now I do feel like I try to be
a little bit
more like open about dating or trying to
at least meet with somebody to see if
they're that person or if there's a
possibility you know like um but it's
been it's definitely it's been
interesting yeah but I like that that
that you know the next phase is supposed
to come into the universe and then what
that what is that going to be like and
how are you just part of the stepping
stone for yeah the next part of life
because in a way that's really all you
are like we have a ton of thoughts
about like if you just saw two animals
go hump in the woods somewhere and then
two months later they had a child you'd
be like oh it seems but if they were
like pining around if you followed one
of the animals for like four years
before and he's just like [__]
rubbing his wiener up against a bush and
[__] you know like coming on you know
just [__] chasing like you know other
animals and [__] and you like watching
all his thoughts he's like sleeping in
the woods and [__] drinking dirty
water to get [__] up and stuff you'd
be like God getting dumb tattoos this
yeah yeah he rolls up like yeah if
animals were like us and they [__]
rolled up with all these dumb tattoos
and [__] CrossFit memberships and
[__] and he's
[__] holy [__] man like yeah old
exercise video DVDs in their
nest like God animal take it easy on
yourself man one of these days nature is
just going to send the right lioness
along and it'll all make sense you know
yeah exactly like think of like what got
you to where you're at now and then when
you really look at it like obviously you
made a choice to work hard I think that
is something we have control over I
chose work you chose to work hard but
then if you look at all
the all the people who helped you and
all the people you met and all The
Inspirations you got around a corner you
didn't expect to turn down and all those
things at some point you have to be like
I I I don't know how much of this I'm
responsible for 100% other than working
hardart so if that's the case for for
everything good in a person's life it's
going to be the same for meeting you
know the a a person that you are going
to be with in a serious way in like in a
marriage situation because I think you
rush the [__] or you um or or or more
importantly
you pretend you're having the feeling
that this is the person you'll spend
forever with versus really having the
feeling
because there's night and day difference
between the two you get into trouble you
can't pretend you have to listen CU you
know you I mean it's nuts man like you
you just knew huh man it was the
weirdest it was so weird and were we all
at a park or something where we all
at where you saw your lady at oh yeah I
was doing a um a a comedy show and she
was friends with my friend and um yeah
she had just come there cuz like he like
yeah she's hanging out and then we were
hanging out and then it was like it's
weird it was weird man it was just
like Fusion or I can't explain it I mean
this is not to say it was perfect no
it's not to say like credits roll movie
like happy you know romantic movie score
I mean I don't think any marriage could
possibly be like that but it was just I
don't know how to explain it it's like
oh yeah we are already married in some
weird way it's like it's like Rippling
backwards through time who knows maybe
it's phones you know what I'm you know
maybe the materials are right and it's
just like her enough of the stink was on
my stink and her stink was a good like
combination of stinks yeah you know
maybe but I don't know I feel like it
was something bigger than that I think
it will be for you too it will be and
then you'll be like holy [__] wow I'm
[__] married I have kids I've
abandoned all that
freedom what have I done yeah I'm just
kid I'm just kidding I'm just [__]
kidding look some of that makes sense
yeah well the [__] the snake has to shed
it skin or the snake dies that's what I
start to feel too I remember a few years
ago I was sitting in uh I was doing an
episode of king and the sting podcast
because I us work on there with Brennan
sha and Christal lean and Eric Griffin I
don't know Chris is on there yet but I
remember thinking like I remember
talking about to them like do we evolve
like when do we
evolve you know like when do are there
times in our lives as humans where we
like I was almost asking the world I
feel like when I think back on that
moment CU I was surprised that I was
thinking about it or asking about it but
I was like when do we evolve when do I
evolve and I didn't know what it meant
really and I still don't exactly but
I think I was looking to evolve at that
point and I think a lot of that was
probably from that iasa experience that
stuff's so powerful you know have you
been through it not yet I'm a little
afraid I mean I've I've you know I've
smoked EMT like everybody else so I've
experienced like some taste of what it
must be but a 4our thre hour DMT trip
just sounds completely life altering
like and and I know many people who have
benefited massively from it uh so I will
eventually do it but yeah I mean dude
you here's one
idea you don't need to evolve actually
the evolution is just realizing where
you're at right now is perfect that's
the evolution it's letting go of the
fantasy of some future better version of
you and loving yourself right now
instead of crucifying yourself on what
you should be or could be this is
perfect not just like the nice parts of
you the whole spectrum is great and that
if you can really like just let yourself
play around with that you do you take a
vacation from self-hate or whatever
though or for most people it's not
self-hate though that that term gets
thrown around a lot it's more like self
like tiny
microaggressions against oneself tiny
moments where you like judge yourself as
being you know somehow unevolved or not
enough or messed up or broken or
whatever yeah and and and then you know
what happens for a lot of people doing
that they get hit by a [__] car
crossing the street they never evolved
they died their last thought was hating
themselves or I didn't order a bus yes
dude so like this is the to me that's
the anytime and I'm not able to do I'm
very neurotic and quite often I will
like get down on myself but anytime I'm
a
especially in the midst of like really
bad times to not
resist that to just like this is what's
happening I'm part of the universe and
right now I [__] stink and I'm tired
and I'm annoyed and I was just an
[__] to the guy putting door knobs on
the door in my house but this is where
I'm at right now this is it yeah somehow
that's where the aggression that causes
all the things we wish we didn't do
dissipates and then suddenly you're just
the universe again you're just part of
the web of everythingness and it's
really a delight yeah yeah yeah I know
there are moments like that I had a
couple moments this morning I just hit
my knees I was like God I just I can't
do anything right nothing is you know
just let me just be a part of the world
let me just realize none of this matters
I'm not going to there's nothing I'm
going to do today that's going to change
the [__] world there's nothing I'm
going to do today that's going to alter
my life in some huge way let me just try
and be palatable to other people today
you know dude I love it that and I think
that is a noble aspiration and I think
that that is a Wonder everyone dude I
know cuz I'm guilty of it man I like I
instantaneously want to be better when
I'm sick I want to be better tomorrow
when I'm like when I'm too fat I want to
lose the [__] weight tomorrow yeah I
don't want the slow boil I want it
instantaneously change and the whole
universe doesn't work like that nothing
works like that except bad things you
can like instantaneously make yourself
worse yeah like 911 yes but the good
stuff it's slow like it's like the the
comparison gets made
to one way to think of your life is like
Rising Sun versus Setting Sun and like
look at the way the sun rises it is so
so for such an incredibly powerful event
it's so weirdly slow like the way the
light gradually changes that's anyone's
life and that's that's why it's like
[__] man a temporary Cloud passes in
front of a sunrise and it might seem
like it's becoming night again but
that's just a it's a cloud yeah you know
it's get the sun's Rising you know
what's happening and you just start
trusting that and then at least for me
you know I become less it's it's just a
paradoxical because somehow by not
attempting to elevate myself to some
super egoic spiritual position i' I
that's where happiness seems to appear
yeah just trust in the sun just trust in
the speed of the sun you know yeah trust
in the speed of the sun it's been there
for a long time it'll be it knows what
it's doing I think it knows what it's
doing yeah yeah at this point let's rely
on a few things that know what they're
doing you know yeah you can trust the
sun I mean maybe not this they were
getting apparently we're getting blasted
by solar flares not to [__] up whatever
spiritual Apex we just
hit it's we're getting blasted by like I
don't know class 50 flares they're like
the internet's going to go down bring
them on man in general you can trust the
sun yeah in general yeah yeah this is a
general
hypothesis um
yeah you know I think it's been
interesting I've been dealing with my
own ego too in the past year that's been
interesting you know as life gets busier
yeah and as uh my ego is very scary to
me you know the ego is very scary I feel
like well how do you describe your ego
what's your just like moments where I
notice that I think I'm deserving of
things or I expect things and I can't
tell if some of it's just because I'm
busier so you need things to kind of fun
you know you get used to some but it's
like I want to be able to show up in
like my best way all the time you know
and so so then it takes more work to
kind of like cultivate and nurture that
best way of yourself you know
um and just kind of rolling with the you
know it's like uh so yeah I think the
ego really scares me because you don't
know what it is you know it's the the
ego is always there yeah it's like your
Shadow it's always connected to you and
it
can it's such a trickster you know and
you can it can uh make you feel
deservant of things it can make you feel
um smarter than PE you know it's like
you I I just have to be care I I just
I'm it's just something that's been kind
of like on my mind think D it's so it's
so embarrassing the ego is the source of
embarrassment because it's just like oh
my dude what the [__] Theo wants me to
do his podcast again what the [__] why
why won't he do mine well he must hate
me does he secretly hate me I wonder if
Theo Von secretly hates me that's you
just told me you're in a bad spot not
once was my ego compassionate not once
was I like he's probably got a lot going
on he's probably not feeling who knows
what it is there's many times you have
like [__] up sending an email or or or
like been in a rotten depressed state
and have not wanted to talk to anybody
no didn't cross my ego's mine yeah my
ego Puffs out gets butt hurt limps
around it's like h
it's so em it's so embarrassing it's so
embarrassing but to react to the
ego in the negative to then go to war
with that poor part of yourself that
poor sad ape in a
cave Part of Yourself disabled veteran
[__] sh you know uh ship captain of a
ve of nobody else on the ship poor
[__] thing it's been trying to
protect you your whole life life and
it's exhausted when you were a kid you
developed it because you needed it to
keep you safe and now it's so tired it
doesn't make as much sense anymore it's
like I guess that's dangerous [__] that
guy we got to punish that person I think
I don't
know you know so some comp like I'm not
don't succumb to the poor thing but when
you realize that's been one of your
number one Shield bearers I know for the
entirety of your life and then suddenly
everyone's like I'm going to take enough
Bast to evaporate you [__] it's
like what I've been I've been protecting
you you yeah I'm just getting EU
euthanize you your teeth are falling out
[__] you it's so sad dude I wonder if we
didn't be if our ego walked in the room
if we'd be in what it would look like
bro that would be such a crazy game show
what if we're what if we're able to get
to a point one time in existence where
our e where people have to show your ego
it's like move that bus who was that
dude that used to do that move that bus
let me hit that dude I would never Ty
Pennington yeah Ty Pennington dude used
to do move that and people were like
show your ego and then it's just some
[__] like maybe like a a [__] comes
out playing like a [__] trumpet you
know and he's got a bunch of [__] with
him like oh damn my ego is [__]
everybody's ego would have a much bigger
dick than
like everybody's ego would have an
enormous
[__] my bald spot would be gone I would
have embarrassing flowing locks I think
I might have a gold chain like I think
there would be gold chains and there
would definitely be spandex
involved maybe like a fashion cane yeah
and somebody carrying a microwave for
you that just makes unlimited pancakes
coming out of it yeah yeah yeah there
would have to be yeah your ego would
like you would also have to present your
ego's imaginary Entourage like all the
people your ego fantz is being
surrounded by one of mine would be China
that wrestler that died a long time ago
Dude oh [__] yeah I know I would want
yeah I would definitely want uh somehow
I don't know why I'd want like Stephen A
lot of Steven step Spielberg Stephen
King stepen Hawking and you know I would
want to be surrounded on one side by all
like these incredible creators that I
respect who like were coming to me for
inspiration and then on the other side
just an ocean of beautiful women like
weeping for me there would be a cult
sort of thing happening for my ego too
Seline Dion there maybe some Seline Dion
some yeah Dion Sanders maybe Dion
Sanders about Seline Dion Sanders
D oh my God you know what a you know I
think you could animate that show
actually I think there is a way you
could like act you could do that show
without having to have some futuristic
technology but people would have to be
completely honest with you and not
afraid to and I think it would be good
for the world oh yeah when all of a
sudden everyone Witnesses oh [__]
everyone's got the same thing I have
riding around in the roller coaster
that' be good it's good for people it
would be good yeah I think there would
be interesting if there were game shows
that were more bearing of our soul Souls
you know in ways um maybe that will come
as we get more technology that tells us
more about what's going on like that's
the plane we're missing a lot of times
with a lot of like uh
medical Intuition or Discovery through
like MRIs and like it's like I wish
there was another type of MRI like we
were saying in the beginning that could
evaluate where we are what lap is our
soul on what are we you know so then
it's like when you met somebody like oh
I see what's going on here it's like
really get some Intel this guy's on his
6,000th lap this dude was in Egyptian
for [__] 2,000 years or this dude is
his first run ever and he's based out of
Minnesota you know yeah this [__]
[__] was Hitler and now he's like
driving an Amazon delivery
truck what the [__] so let's just get
him what he
needs you're a great artist no really
you're an incredible artist
I love your art please don't do another
Holocaust dude I'll buy the painting
it's great whatever you want nfts oh
he's making nfts buy the [__] nfts
just buy them it doesn't
matter dude it's crazy well when our
body starts to did you see that video
you see that Tito Ortiz can you pull
that out there was a Tito Ortiz video
where he hit mock seven or eight whoa
and it shows
you I think it made me think about wow
what what's goes on inside of us and
what a shell our body
is yeah man yeah man it's so wild it's
the there's a whole ecosystem happening
in there a whole psychic ecosystem I
know and there's like turtles in it
there's everything dude a turtle swam up
on the beach the other day in Maui and
uh I went to vacation and a turtle was
there and uh it was just Fascinating
People like going up and seeing it and
spending time by it they're so mystical
the the Hawai and turtles are like holy
creatures you feel lucky to be around
them they're just they're so beautiful
you ever go scuba diving um no you see
them in the W I mean when you see them
on Shore obviously that's like not their
best on Shore they're kind of clumsy
slow but in the water holy [__] they're
just you know they seem like they would
Grant a wish or something yeah they're
beautiful well it makes sense then and
that's one thing
what is this thank you friend this is
Tito Ortiz yeah passes out he hit nine
G's who is I'm so sorry T Ortiz is a UFC
was a UFC wrestler he is a um he's also
he does one thing that's really neat
about him he does all of the
uh uh meals at the Laugh Factory he goes
there and passes out food that's cool on
Thanksgiving um he's a philanthropic
dude that's cool um and he's a famous uh
UFC fighter can we go back and yeah
let's see that video but watch what
happens it's interesting to see what
happens to the Shell of us at certain uh
levels
yeah Max
per
this how
you you don't want to me don't
toile Alex is saying that you have to do
oh [__] that wow he's in
there this is a 9g
simulator holy
[__]
wow how you bu with me
wow go back to that moment where his
face is limp it's kind of fascinating
just to see what your uh and just pause
it right there if you can find it Zach
on that
screen
um oh my God that's I mean right there I
was like wow we are just our B it's just
a such a shell I mean here's a one of
the toughest men you know how old are
you I'm 43 I'm 48 man that is what I
look like when I wake up
that's you got to sew it back together I
had to like push it up electri shck to
get the things to work
again yeah that's crazy that that's yeah
the mask is just sort of drooping off
the skull the eyes yeah man that's
that's [__] and that's almost a way of
looking at your Eno that's a
that's a ego uh deflating moment to have
this moment just be out there for him
that's pretty cool just like this is if
you let my body just if let let me show
you what it is at its un uh refined form
you know this is you know Rogan talks
about like this is like the benefit of
martial arts or like you know because
you're you you're you're getting beaten
up like I I don't know much about it I'm
guessing in front of the planet he's
been knocked out maybe or defeated I
don't know and once that happens to you
that you know whatever it is the
insecurity and stuff you already got you
know you you know that you are not
perfect you know you're going to lose
fights you know the way you got good at
fighting is not by winning every fight
and so apparently there's like a benefit
to that you know to to knowing where
you're at you know that's why he does
stuff like that that's and all you know
man anytime you get around like
Mo anytime I've been around Rogan and we
get to be around like a a famous
fighter they are weirdly similar to
people at the Romos Retreats really
they've got this glow to them I mean
again I'm making a blanket assessment
for a few people I've met no no oh yeah
there's something fascinating about them
it's almost like seeing some of them
it's like being around one of those
Turtles kind of yes they have this holy
quality to them or the spiritual
component and and they you would almost
forget
the person you're sitting next to if for
whatever reason they decided to they
would be the last person you saw you
would like see them lunge towards you
and that's it you're dead you you're
dead you just forget it's like hanging
around a really well behaved pit or
something you forget and and also
because it's just so sweet they're so
sweet and there's something there's
something interesting about being able
to be knocked out like to being able to
put yourself in that risk space you know
of like yes because it's such a
defeating thing you know being knocked
out it's everybody's biggest fear what
if I got I was unconscious in front of
other like you're at you have no control
over yourself you are you
are at a Le at a you are limp you're
limp in front of the planet yeah every
your your your wife might be in the
audience your kids are in the audience
watching daddy your ego yeah your ego is
like what the the [__] yeah you [__]
[__] look at you I told you to [__]
dope I told you to use that new
synthetic [__] testosterone the
Russians
developed yeah man I that's like yeah
it's you there's something about you
know okay I don't know if you're
familiar are you you're probably
familiar with Jack caroak the beat poets
so I used to think the beat poets as
they're called kowak I guess Ginsburg
falls into that category what about uh
what's his name who was all uh
um vaget was he a beat poet no I think
he was at the same time period but I
don't know for sure I wish I were more
literary than I he wasn't really in like
the beat pack beatpack was that kowak um
you know uh who else William Burrows
burrow that's right Kowski kind of gets
lumped in there a little bit Yeah does
Ginsburg land there or was I totally
okay no Ginsburg is there too so so like
I used to think beat meant like like the
Dr the beat of like I don't know a Congo
or some [__] you know they would all
wear turtlenecks and like have drum
circles or there's Jazz but what I read
is it means defeated we're beat we've
already been beat we lost it's over we
beat we're not trying to win anymore and
that the in that place being beat that's
where you find Freedom that's where you
find true Liberation you're you've
disconnected from the [__] horrible
drums that drive the ship of capitalism
it doesn't mean you're they're obviously
not failing they're writing beautiful I
mean kowak wrote on the road apparently
in what what was it one night two nights
on speed wow he took just like in those
days I don't know what kind of speed
they had it was like on paper strips or
something so he just got blasted on
speed right it's one of the Great
American Road novels in a couple of
nights [__] infuriating man so it's
not like they were like we're beat
taking bong hits doing camine playing
God of War it's
like not that that's the worst
experience no but that's yeah you know
what I mean so it's but but that state
of consciousness of like yeah like I'm
already I think we're another way to put
it would be at least we're beat in the
sense you're not going to do better than
the UN than the earth you're not going
to like d right there's yeah yeah you're
not fighting this invisible you're not
in this battle that you cannot really
win you're kind of like accepting that
hey this is where things are you know
let me operate from a place of I am not
the king yes and it's such a wonderful
thing to stop trying to save the [__]
planet it's such a wonderful thing to
stop trying to be because you the ego is
so deceptive that it will convince you
that you are demonstrating some
altruistic imp
yes when really you want to be the
godamn Messiah you want to be Jesus you
want to like save the you want to be the
only person who saves the planet you
want the credit for you know what I
mean yeah yeah that's real scary man
yeah I've noticed there were moments
like that I remember a few years ago
whenever I started to get like uh just
people would come out to my shows and
stuff I started thinking oh does God
have some special plan for me you know
like and that was very scary to me just
didn't know and I was like what if I'm
not doing things right or like what if I
can't handle this type of if I just had
never had like
um you know it's scary when people come
to spend time with you know it's like
why me you know you start asking and
then your ego will start answering
sometimes if you're not [__] you know
if you don't have some inkling or some
guidance or hearing good things from
people that are helping you navigate
things um sure but I remember that I
remember thinking man I I'm not going to
be able to be a leader you know so this
is real scary now I'm going to half how
do I pretend to be a leader you know and
then that eventually kind of went away
and I realized that that was a Fool's
Gold thing but sure it was very scary I
remember when that happened I was like
[__] like but to think that yeah like
I'm just a part of this thing and and
we've all we're all defeated how do we
operate now right you know what now like
now and and I'll tell you man if you
look at the like like the Messiah or God
is being like if you look at the Messiah
as being not a a the the next Messiah
the second coming of Christ whatever you
want to call it the mraa if you look at
it not as being one person but rather a
harmonized uh group of God knows how
many people or just think about Jesus
like I don't know how many people talk
about like Jesus's
like or or think of Mary who is Mary's
great-grandfather right like Mary's
great-grandfather if Mary the ver I me
forgive me if this seems vulgar I don't
mean to be offensive but okay you know
what I'll replace Messiah think of like
the Buddha's great grandmother like
imagine if that great grandmother
decided not to let someone ejaculate
inside of her just the exact right time
and hadn't raised that you kid in the a
certain way there would be no Buddha so
it's like when you start looking at the
fact that like we all part of not just
like the shitty things the planet spits
out but theoretically you could be
wouldn't you like to be one pixel in the
the Buddha one pixel one cell one little
tiny part of whatever the next thing is
that like just shakes the planet to its
foundations in the positive I would
that's enough that would be cool you
want to be the whole [__] thing
that's insane that's the ego it's like
you won't you you know there's a story
Ram's brother I guess that's great man
that's a great way to say that that's a
great way to say that like how can I
just be a cell in the wellness of
whatever you know or how do I just show
up enough to be a part of things in a
positive way you know and trust that you
are right then you get to have that
thing that your ego is looking for but
in a much more realistic in much more
interactive way like now you you don't
and and you know all the great stories I
mean God look at what Jesus said when he
sent out the disciples I think it was
something something along the lines of
don't worry what you're going to say I'm
going to speak through you and if people
don't accept you shake the dust from
your sandals and just that's just leave
no big deal just for you don't have to
worry that's that's what I love about
Christianity is that you you don't have
to worry anymore like you're taken care
of now you you you don't need to worry
you don't have to and so yeah I think
like you know from that perspective you
don't have to like plan yeah what the
[__] you're going to do to become M de
or whatever and have like a Legions of
people worshiping you as you drive some
like I me whatever the [__] is
Corvette or whatever probably or a te-
bird maybe yeah yeah you don't have to
yeah that's one cool thing that's nice
about I mean I go to 12ep I go to
recovery programs and so that's one one
of the coolest things I feel is when I'm
in those rooms and it's like people are
listening to each other and everybody's
there for the goodness of one another
yeah there's a feeling I leave out of
there with like man I'm a part of
something that feels good you know and
it doesn't feel like it's about me it
feels like just a part of something that
feels good and I think everybody like I
think there's a
general I think as a society we're like
have we I wonder if we'll look back on
our society like if thousands of years
from now they'll look back and like man
what a wrong turn that we because we're
just this ship in the water that's all
humanity is like and man we took such a
we learned a ton but what a turn that
was going along those ways of of uh
thinking that we had all the answers and
that science was going to lead us to the
to the be all end all and that we were
gonna be able to crack the code like
what a what a exhilarating and
exhausting [__] experiment that was
yeah right let's just you know well I
mean I think the I love the parable of
the prodigal son it's so good for
Humanity it's not just good for an
individual life you know the prodal son
story
synopsis there's
a dad there's a kid who there's a I'm
sorry basically there's two brothers one
of them decid decides to stay at his
father's house and help with a farm
essentially and the other is like I'm
out of here and leaves and just goes on
this like
hedonistic Voyage Through Life
prostitutes blows all his [__] money
ends up Brad Pit was it was Brad Pit in
it it's
not it's a parable for the Bible but it
would be an amazing Brad Pit movie a
beautiful man but the the essentially
this kid ruins his life he becomes some
kind like a pig farmer which apparently
back then was like the worst thing you
could be and so in shame and humiliation
he realizes I'm going to have to move
back in with my dad like all the [__] I
said about how I was going to be a
famous break dancer whatever [__] he
was saying it didn't happen
[Laughter]
and which also let me tell you this if
you're telling your dad you're going to
be a famous break dancer nine out of
nine
times you're probably not gonna I don't
know the statistics on it but it's got
to be worse than famous comedian it's
got to be much more improbable so yeah
basically the story is he he goes back
home and his dad takes one look at him
and he's a he's like legitimately like I
[__] up I let my ego take control I
thought I was going to be able to do the
caterpillar and moonwalk or whatever the
[__] and I suck at dancing body rolls
and all that body rolls and what I love
about at least the version of I read is
before you can finish the apology his
father Embraces him before he can even
finish the apology and says like let's
throw a huge party we're going to throw
this massive celebration meanwhile the
other brother is out in the [__]
field and like realizes what's happening
he's like how come you never throw a
party for [__] me I didn't go try to
become a break dancer I didn't buy
embarrassing parachute [__] pants and
crypto and do start [__] nft AI
company or try to like use AI to sell my
stickers on [__] Etsy what the [__]
I've been out here with the
oxen what happened well his his father
says um to the son like you know we're
celebrating you've been here you've been
alive you're alive you've been here
we're celebrating because that which was
dead has come back to life that's the
celebration he my son was gone lost dead
now that now he's back this is the joy
so what you're talking about with the in
any individual life especially like when
you finally get into a 12 step program
you break that addiction dude and you
look at your life when you were tanking
your [__] life on blow and booze and
you look at out you weren't even there
you weren't even there you were dead you
didn't exist if you look back you were
blacking out you were [__] up you
weren't there it was a wa at the very
best awaking dream and you can't
remember a lot of that [__] and then
suddenly holy [__] you start coming back
to life that's what it's about for the
individual but for what you're saying is
like for Humanity as a whole I think
that's what's so beautiful about it is
there's the possibility for the entirety
of the species to reorient itself into
another way of being and and and at
least because you know it's obviously in
the Bible it's theistic the message is
God doesn't care how much money you
spent on the stupid break dancer clothes
you were wearing or your failed Etsy
business or all the people you lied to
or all the people you stabbed in the
back as long as those things brought
brought you back
home that's all that matters as long as
you're able to come and say I'm sorry
and mean it that's what I love about
that story and I think like that's what
Humanity has to look forward to probably
I do I think yeah maybe we did right now
we're like [__] scooping up pig [__]
or whatever and pretending it's gold but
I have a feeling like you know we'll
come back around we'll come back around
yeah if a person can come back around
all of us can come back around yeah cuz
all we are is just a person really we're
all just one person you're saying you're
right man just one very
complex very very big person yeah and
you have to and yeah you have to start
thinking how do we all win as a spe like
how what little part can I do to help us
be a part of that or not even what can I
do but how do I just operate in a way
that uh behooves everyone and how can I
do that more today yeah that's it it's a
nice question to have each day each day
how can I do that more today for my
fellow man yeah for my fellow specic
member yeah um it's a good question and
sometimes you will not be able to answer
it no yeah some sometimes you'll go
you'll and you'll you'll slink back off
and but I think having of that as like a
uh as a good question is nice and that's
a neat thing about life is sometimes
once certain things get introduced to
you you can't unintroduced them you know
yes and that's one thing that's really
cool it's like man once you kind of
see a little bit of the light you can't
unsee it you know no that's one thing
that's neat about getting in a recovery
programs even like you were saying like
you were dead like once you can look
back and see that like oh I wasn't a
contributing member to myself yeah to
anyone I wasn't able to love my sister I
wasn't able to love my brother I wasn't
able to love myself and like how you can
start to you know do those do those
things better yeah man and being you
know uh the times I've been in those
rooms when you it's what's cool about it
is you see people who like you thought
you hit bottom like you see people who
like [__] they did the same thing
China's doing right now we like they're
trying to dig a hole to the Center of
the Earth you're like are you kidding me
what the [__] you know the stories are
crazy but then the fact that you're
looking at them they're healthy they're
they're happy they're doing great that
is where you realize how incredibly
powerful it is to be a human yes cuz
they sure as [__] shouldn't have climbed
out of that hole yeah some of those
holes man you know what I'm talking
about there's seven yeah there's seven
story holes dude eight stories 12
stories like how did you get a hole this
deep how did you even do it yeah you
didn't even have a shovel like if I told
someone I'm going to pay you I will pay
you 500,000 th000 to destroy your life
in this way they wouldn't be able to do
it and these people did it just with
whiskey like
inhalent it's
like oh that's [__] cool man what uh
what time we at Zach um like 2 hours 20
minutes something like that a little
under
okay um trying to think of something
else I wanted to think about with you
you were talking about sex in a
graveyard I can actually chime in on
that I worked with a guy at a pizza shop
who uh this is a true story I delivered
pizzas with this guy Steve and he would
take his wife they had kids he they
would hire sitter every Saturday and
they would go [__] have sex in a
graveyard are you [__] kidding me
yeah yeah his wife's name was Angel she
was 390 lb what and were they Mexican
because a lot of Mexicans they weren't
no white trash Ohio a lot of Mexicans go
that's one thing I love that Mexicans do
they do that Elia deos Muertos you know
and they go celebrate in the graveyard
with the deceased Mexicans it's a big
part of the culture like if you're in La
you can go on Halloween to the
graveyards and it is like you know it's
like a damn Selena you know like concert
the Hollywood Forever Cemetery has it's
it's incredible it's awesome it's
beautiful and it's not you expect it to
be like morbid or Grim but it isn't at
all it's celebratory it's beautiful you
could see how they're honor ing these
people it's really incredible yeah I
mean you can eat an empanada with a
700-year old Mexican
dude you know yes yeah you
can oh yeah The Ramones are buried there
that's right that cemetery is pretty
wild it is it's and they that's where I
don't know if they do it anymore but
they used to do movies there like on the
weekends and Stu I think they still do I
actually went with James Blake he's a
musician he's been on here before he's a
really really amazing British producer
and musician and he um he and I went to
Elia deos muos one time and they had
music and they had yeah just Mexican
family just sitting with their deceased
ancestors you know it's really sweet I
mean it's so so sophisticated like the
way a lot of people do death is really
like [__] up you try not to think
about it you just try like someone dies
and you know you just try to put them
out of out of your head I mean I've and
they don't and they don't really
disappear it's funny cuz I can think
about my father right and I can think
about how he feels how his I can think
about what he wears I can think about
his voice is alive inside of my head and
in my heart I can feel it I can um I can
put my hand on my heart and it's his
heartbeat like Parton of my the beat of
my heart was made by two other people's
beats it's a m it's a [__] song yeah
that's inside of me that was created by
you know so it's
really we really do do that poorly I
think in in uh or I've done that poorly
in my life is
honoring
um the deceased you know honoring the
people that put their time in so I could
exist you know maybe part of the problem
is it's so bizarre when you lose someone
when you realize somehow even though
they're bodies aren't here they're
closer than they've ever been to you
like you have the sense no they're here
I mean not like a ghost paranormal way
but like something deeper than that just
like what you're saying and you don't
you it's hard for people to deal with
that it's almost heartbreaking in a in a
way or you're afraid to connect with
them you have a sense anytime you do
they've just been waiting for you to
reach out oh that's interesting it's
almost a shamed there's a little bit of
Shame if I were to sit and really just
go spend time like in a room or in an
open field and tell my father I wanted
to talk to him or spend time with
part of me would feel a shame that it
took me so long to do it yeah yeah and
you know what I've when I've like
presented that shame to like my
mom's Soul or whatever you want to call
that the response is
always I love you yeah they don't
there's no like why didn't you [__]
use IA to talk to me you you know it's
just a sense of like I love you so much
enjoy your life
enjoy your life you're doing great I
love you it's this place is for love
nothing else that's always been the the
the sort of the message you
know I I it's I they don't seem to even
see shame or right on the I think
whatever it is why were you watching
Date Line they're never like
that why why why the [__] were you
obsessed with Keith Morrison yeah why
did you work for a week to try to do a
Keith Morrison impression that you could
never pull off
yeah but what about that avocado not bad
thank you not bad yeah man it's just
yeah it's why did you go to that Duran
Duran concert the other night yeah
they're not they just it's it's like I
think whatever is on the other side as
they call it is so beautiful you know
RDA says it's like taking off a shoe
that's too tight it's death death is
like taking off a shoe that's too tight
it's whatever's there is so so beautiful
and so much more real than this place
that beings that are
there they are they just want us to be
happy they are just love you know and
also you know as a parent like if my kid
somehow reaches through the veil to
communicate with me after I'm dead I'm
not going to be like look at your
[__] shitty shirt why do you have
gravy all over your shirt
oil you're not going to be yelling at
change your oil boy I taught you to do
that I taught you you're gonna burn your
engine out it's easy I bought you that
[__] car with the
inheritance yeah dude you're it's like
they just love that's that's it that's
it that's a fundamental fabric of
everything is that kind of energy yeah
and you're right the darkness part is
it's like you know turning on a light
you just turn on the light that's all it
is man it's like the darkness is really
the weakest of things when you consider
how it's so you just flip a light switch
light a candle it's gone yeah wasn't
really there and you usually need other
people to do it you
need yeah that's why isolation kills so
many alcoholics and so many addicts
that's why isolation kill creates so
many School shooters and like severe
like uh uh violent nihilists I niist
means yeah yeah you nihilism the the
the the idea that all you are is atams I
mean if you want to take it to the
furthest point it's like this is this is
essentially an accident Big Bang happens
and Just sh just by like time and
molecules swirling together we became
what did you call it
reactive we became reactive meat earlier
on you had a really nistic description
of human human beings we're just
temporarily sensient we are doomed to
die we didn't ask to be [__] born and
here we are Mortals in a universe of
infinite atoms but whatever we are it's
just a [__] accident like just a a
bad collision between the wrong organic
molecules a long time ago and some
oxygen and some [__] oxygen and [__]
it and then do you believe that's true
or not no I don't believe that's true at
all my experience of life is the
opposite of that and it's interesting
because I feel like we've created a
society kind of in the U in America
where if you're not careful you can kind
of you can get lapped in a beli in that
we have a society that really you know
we sat we've created that a lot of
things that mean a lot to us or that
should or really just um wears for sale
yeah or that that um even our important
moments or I don't know I feel like it
we there's been some deviation but I
think there's like you're saying there's
there's a lot if you cannot see that if
you can find other people and listen to
if you can just be open to possibility
it's you can quickly get back to a place
that feels good yes because that's what
you actually are right the place that
feels good is you right fundamental
goodness there's that's you that's
ground level whatever you want to call
it bedrock yeah the Bedrock and
everything else is just defense
mechanisms and yeah and and yeah exactly
you'll know when you're there CU you're
already the Paradox is you're already
there and it's just like there so many
comparisons uh it's like a lantern
that's got a lot of like dirt or dust on
it you know what I mean your your
soul is the light the lantern is your
countless incarnations and once you
clear away the dust boom there you are
again and that's the weird I don't know
if you had it with iasa but with DMT
that's that weird
familiarity people report which I
certainly experienc where you're like oh
I know this place there was nothing to
be afraid of this is just a place of
love and joy and delight and [__] I've
been so hard on myself yeah I I was a
cockroach for 50
incarnations just like you said earlier
what was I do what was I doing beating
myself up yeah I'm doing great I'm doing
great yeah and and truly if you're a
human at least from the Buddhist
perspective they it's the Rarity of the
human Incarnation from the Buddhist
cosmology like they think there's more
Gods than there are humans that if you
are lucky enough to be born a human
you've really you probably weren't a
cockroach like you have done some heavy
lifting to land in the human realm and
especially you know there's a weird kind
of like
Multiverse aspect of Buddhism a lot of
people don't know about but to be born
in a realm where there was a Buddha
where there was a Jesus I mean you pick
your Messiah where because there's
there's the possibility of being born in
a time when nobody had any kind of
spiritual technology developed so to be
in a in a world where that we have like
volumes volumes of like incredible
spiritual technology that anytime you
want you can connect to is very good
karma very good fortune a great point
it's very good fortune do you think if
if they if they proved aliens if there
was some proof of them like and
obviously if there was some further
proof that really set in everybody like
everybody it was
like you
know was like wow they're there they're
out there would what would that do to
religion do you think that would
strengthen it or do you think that would
weaken it well I mean I you know I think
it depends on on the religion and the
lineage of the religion I mean if you've
been living in a religion that is doing
the same thing for Humanity that we used
to do for planet Earth the Earth was the
center of the universe so if you've been
living in some mindset that humanity is
the you know the sum total of or like
the the final part of God's creation or
something then yeah it's going to [__]
with your head because now you have to
deal with the fact that no there's the
universe is teeming with life on every
level from the subatomic to the like to
to to to giant planets to God knows what
to the point where we might be some
Atomic portion of something we'll never
understand so yeah but I think you know
a lot of religions already have built in
the idea that we're talking about the
source of all reality kind of
superintelligent
prenative uh benevolent Creator Force
that just Delights in making stuff and
delights in like
sharing its Creation with the things it
makes and we get to co-create with it it
invites us to like sit down at the
potter's wheel with it and make stuff
while we're here so it's a really
wonderful artist whoever it is whatever
it is and it's the best kind of artist
doesn't like where are the there's no
signatures there's no copyright there's
no IP it's claiming for the some total
of all things it's that incredible it's
it's like
Banksy nobody knows who Banksy is it's
like that it's just like here have it
all I'm giving you all of it let's see
what you do with it yeah it's beautiful
so I think from that perspective aliens
sure why not and what if aliens sh they
also had a God too what if they rolled
up with a couple Gods we did we would
figure it out well yeah that would
that's where it would that's what that's
what would be so exciting it's like what
who do they believe in who are you
worshiping who is your god what is an
alien god like and what do they think of
our idea of God or what if they're like
all like Richard [__] Dawkins and
they're pissed at us like there's no god
you dumb shits we made you we your
[__] god look at his big black eyes
emotionless face we made you you just
hallucinated all the other stuff because
we built that into you to like believe
in a God because that makes you easy to
control
we would beat them up then we would oh
dude I think we would I think we would
fight to have a God the first alien
human world star fight like when a human
finally just punches an alien it's weird
to think our kids might see that man
it's weird to think that we might
see I don't think there's a lot of beef
between black I have some black friends
and they said there's a lot of beef
between like blacks and Aliens too what
yeah that's like we don't hear about cuz
we're not you know I guess in that
culture that much but yeah there's a lot
of
like black alien what yeah they don't
get along I or they don't yeah they
don't get along that much I mean how
many black dudes you even know are like
yeah who have like alien posters or
anything like that you know I mean I I
honestly I don't know anyone who has
alien posters but like I do know black
people who are like super into aliens I
but oh maybe I got to meet more black
folks then you know maybe who knows it's
like I I don't know I mean I get I know
there's a lot of people who like are
think they're demons I mean that's one
of the threads
of of of of like that's one of the
explanations for them is it's like no
these are the legions of Satan coming to
the Earth to pose as aliens and trick us
into getting on those [__] ships
don't get on the ships yeah don't get on
the ships cuz they're going to fly you
right to Hell [__] don't get on
the ships I'm going to want to go look
at least on there I bet well yeah of
course me too we will get on the ships
but I'm going to say hey tell me before
y'all leave no dude you will get on the
ship for sure I guarantee you'll get on
the ship I guarantee it we'll probably
be podcasting on a spaceship at some
point I mean maybe that is what we're on
who knows maybe that's a part of it they
get you on the ship they make you forget
you're on a ship they trick you into
thinking you're in the human Dimension
we're just in some Cargo Bay right now
plugged into the Matrix
baby that's awesome man uh Duncan thanks
so much for your time dude anytime Theo
Hit that [__] one more time this was
such a so fun yeah so fun man so fun to
see you again and um yeah we should
probably just do one to follow up this
one I think people will love this this
has been one of my favorite chats in a
while man dude M too thank you I really
think you're wonderful and thank you so
much for having me on your show it means
the world thank you yeah 100% man I want
to do it again soon and uh and we'll do
yours yeah we can just zoom it from
wherever if I'm back in town great
wonderful yeah I'll I'll hit you up do
you ever do them live um I'm you know
I'm building a podcast studio right now
but it's slow going you can talk to this
company here too they're really good you
know I'm I'm tempted to honestly because
I've been trying to do it at home and
I'm just wondering if that's like a
little bit bit like kind of what we were
talking about earlier like you got to
shed that that skin like why do you want
to do it at home what are you doing like
why not expand do it like you're doing
this is one of the things like you
sigura Rogan it's like you know you guys
are real Trend Setters you're really
leading the charge as far as like
creating your own TV show basically and
like making it look good having a nice
studio and stuff and I don't know it
just takes so much work yeah this I just
I just started working with this company
called Rooster Teeth and they've been
awesome man it's been good it's been
really just interesting um and I'm glad
that they've been supportive but yeah it
is I think you know there's something
nice about having it at home it feels
homey but I think you feel homey no
matter what no matter where you would be
yeah right you know sometimes I used to
get I started in my kitchen and I was
like oh if I ever leave my kitchen
something will be wrong I won't be able
to communicate correctly or something um
that's how I feel yeah like I'm going to
lose like the vibe of like this is my
garage like this is my gritty podcast
Studio yeah and it's like that's so dumb
like why do I like I want to I want to
expand it just gez man we need your
voice out there I think thanks man it's
really good to hear I've been really I
feel much better than when I came in
today same I feel more
inspired um I feel yeah like I can do
better when I communicate with people um
it's just a really really nice reminder
uh you are a nice reminder of how to
operate in the world thank you Theo hey
man we don't have to podcast you can hit
me up anytime you want if you just want
to shoot the [__] I love talking to you
and I would be thrilled so thanks man
thanks man thanks for having me on the
show yeah we'll do it again soon
beautiful Duncan Trussell ladies and
gentlemen me get a
snap now I'm just floting on the breeze
and I feel I'm falling like these leaves
I must be on a
stone oh but when I reach that ground
I'll share this piece of my I found I
can feel it in my
bones but it's going to take